<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<title>Who is responsible for risk consequencies</title>
<label>Risk Strategy</label>
<intro>Learn more about possible Risk response strategies</intro>
<next>process/risk/risk</next>

<description>
</description>

<keywords>
</keywords>

<term>risk</term>

<text>

    <p>[Risk List](/process/risk/risk}">Risks</a> are defined in a <a href="${url:process/risk/risklist)
    during the [Inception Phase](/process/time/inception)
    and are presented to you prior to the [LCO Milestone](/process/time/lco).
    You have to choose a strategy for each Risk that appears on the list.</p>

    <p>You have two options - either to pay for the implementation of a pro-active Mitigation Plan and eliminate the Risk, or
    to do nothing, but agree that if the Risk happens, you will assume responsibility later by paying for Contingency Plan.</p>

    <p>This following is an example of a possible Risk:</p>

    <table>
        <tr>
            <th>Risk description</th>
            <th>Mitigation Plan</th>
            <th>Contingency Plan</th>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Data provider changes the API on its own schedule, without prior
        notification. The next change may happen before the project
        release Milestone, and the system won't work</td>
        <td>Develop a configurable XML-based integration module that will
        allow dynamic API changes without code re-factoring</td>
        <td>Integration module re-factoring</td>
        </tr>
    </table>

    <p>The numbers for these different plans include:</p>

    <table>
        <tr>
            <th>Plan</th>
            <th>Cost, staff-hours</th>
            <th>Duration, business days</th>
        </tr>

        <tr><td>Mitigation Plan</td><td>140</td><td>7</td></tr>
        <tr><td>Contingency Plan</td><td>280+</td><td>10+</td></tr>
    </table>

    <p>All of these numbers are provided to you prior to the commencement of the project.
    Thus, there is a choice of spending 140 staff-hours immediately to remove the Risk,
    or to do nothing, with the understanding the 280 or more hours may be required later
    at your expense.</p>

    <p>The first option is called <i>mitigation</i> and means that you are ready to
    spend time and money pro-actively in order to guarantee that the Risk will be removed.</p>

    <p>The second option is called <i>acceptance</i>, and means that you do not take any action,
    but is ready to pay later if the Risk does in fact happen. If the Risk never happens, you
    will never pay for it.</p>

    <p>If the Risk is not identified and is not listed in Risk List, the
    Risk is already mitigated, and bears no responsibility for you.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c5 name="process/risk/risk">Risk is an atomic element of a Risk List</c5>
    <c3 name="process/cost/budget">Budget includes Risk responses and Risk reserves</c3>
    <c5 name="process/time/schedule">Schedule also includes Risk responses and Risk Reserves</c5>
</concepts>

</article>


