<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>06/07/07</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. Introduces German Version of Corporate Web Site</title>

<description>A German version of TechnoPark Corp.'s web \site is now available
 at technoparkcorp.de. The new website is targeted at German and
 German speaking businesses in sestern Europe.</description>

<text>

<p>TechnoPark Corp. introduced its new
 <ahref name="http://www.technoparkcorp.de">German-language website</ahref>.
 The company already had web resources in English and Russian.</p> 

<p>With the addition of German support, TechnoPark Corp. expects to
 significant growth in its client base, especially as the company's research
 shows that Indian outsourcing companies are not readily able to
 compete in the German market.</p>  

<p>The conservative business element of Europe is more likely to choose
 "nearshoring" instead of "offshoring" when it comes to contracting out web
  development needs, TechnoPark has found.</p> 

<p>With a wide choice of providers located geographically close to
 their countries, western European businesses generally prefer nearsourcing
 their IT projects to central and eastern Europe. TechnoPark's proven history
 and U.S. division gives it a distinct advantage over the emerging software
 outsourcing destinations of Hungary, Romania, Czech Republic, Belarus,
 Russia and even its home in the Ukraine.</p> 

<p>TechnoPark has isolated three practical reasons why western European
 businesses choose the firm for nearshoring:</p> 

<ol><li><strong>Cultural proximity.</strong> Ukraine's religious and mental
 ties to western Europe are historical.</li>
<li><strong>Time-zone proximity.</strong> There is only a one hour difference
 between timezones in the Ukraine and Germany. The difference is the same with
  most western European locations.</li>
<li><strong>Geographical proximity.</strong> Ukraine is a maximum three hour flight
 from any European country, and there are direct flights from most countries. </li></ol>      

<p>"We chose to start a German division because we have already had successful
 experiences implementing projects for German clients," explains Egor
 Bougaenko, CEO of TechnoPark Corp. "We feel that Germany is a good market,
 so we want to address German businesses in their language."</p> 

<p>For more information on the German division of TechnoPark Corp. visit
 <ahref name="http://www.technoparkcorp.de">www.technoparkcorp.de</ahref>.</p>  

</text>
</article>