<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<terms>

<invisible/>

<acceptancestatement>An Acceptance Statement is a written document signed by both parties when 
Deliverables for Effective Specification are successfully accepted by the customer. 
Accepted Statement is attached to the accepted Specification.</acceptancestatement>

<activities>Activities are units of work performed by TPC in order to create and 
deliver Deliverables, including but not limited to project management, requirements development and 
management, architectural analysis and design, implementation and unit testing, test planning 
and testing, configuration management, and deployment.</activities>

<arbitrator>Arbitrator is a person or organization that is responsible for settling disputes between two parties, as defined in Article XX.</arbitrator>

<baseline>Baseline is an aggregate of Scope, Cost, Schedule, Risk List and Operations Plan.</baseline>

<businessday>Business day is a day when both parties agree to communicate and perform work according to contract, 
business day is defined in par.110.</businessday>

<budget>Budget is the predetermined price a customer shall pay for Deliverables created according to 
Effective Specification. The Budget is attached to the Effective Specification and is approved 
with the Effective Specification. Budget is shown in staff-hours without specific details.</budget>

<confidentialinformation>Confidential Information means any and all proprietary information disclosed 
or made available by one party to another in the course of performing hereunder, 
whether in written, email, instant message, orally by phone, personally, magnetic, photographic, 
optical or other form and whether now existing or hereafter created, including, without 
limitation, all trade secrets, names and contacts of employees and partners, 
technology, data, computer programs, processes, methods, operational procedures, plans, 
strategies or results, and other information of a similar nature that is not generally disclosed by 
such party to the public. Confidential Information shall not include any information which (a) is proven 
by written evidence to have been in a receiving party's possession prior to disclosure by the other 
party; (b) is received from a third party having the right to disclose such information; (c) is 
or hereafter becomes public knowledge through no act or fault of a receiving party; or (d) is 
proven by written evidence independently developed by a receiving party without access to 
the Confidential Information of the other party.</confidentialinformation>

<cost>Cost is the sum of all Budgets for Effective Specifications and Retainers for Beta-Specifications. 
Cost is calculated in staff-hours. Cost may also be referred to as "Cost Baseline".</cost>

<defect>Defect is a non-conformance of Deliverables to Effective Specification or to the accepted Specification. 
Defect includes detailed textual and graphical (if necessary) descriptions of non-conformance 
that allows technical specialists to understand and reproduce the non-conformance.</defect>

<deliverables>Deliverables are products, services and results developed for and/or delivered to a
customer by TPC according to Effective Specification. Deliverables include, if not 
explicitly specified in Effective Specification, source software code, compiled products, 
comments to software code, and Specifications. Deliverables do not include Project Documentation.</deliverables>

<eva>Earned Value Analysis (EVA) is a method used to assess the magnitude of any 
project schedule and cost variations that occur. EV (Earned Value) is the total 
amount of staff-hours planned for Functional Requirements that are accepted; 
PV (Planned Value) is a total amount of staff-hours planned for Functional Requirements 
planned to be approved to date; AC (Actual Cost) is a total amount of staff-hours 
spent for Deliverables to date from Preliminary Specification approval, CPI equals to 
EV divided by AC; SPI equals to EV divided by PV. Wherever referred "EVA numbers" 
include PV, EV, AC, SPI, and CPI.</eva>

<intellectualproperty>Intellectual Property is defined as any ideas, techniques, 
methods, processes, research, developments, documents, work products or idea expressions, 
having either patent, copyright, trade secret, mask work, or any other statutory right 
associated therewith, which are created or generated during the performance of the Deliverables. 
Intellectual Properties may arise under contract, or result from Confidential Information.</intellectualproperty>

<ipr>IPR means Intellectual Property Right for Deliverables.</ipr>

<lco>LCO Milestone (lifecycle objectives) is a Milestone defined for 
Alpha-Specification, meaning the date when Beta-Specification should be created.</lco>

<lcm>License Control Module is a software module installed into Deliverables by TPC that blocks 
normal execution of software within 10 (ten) calendar days after a project starts. License Control 
Module is self-removable software module that destroys itself after a license code is entered. 
License code is provided by TPC to Customer together with IPR transferring.</lcm>

<milestone>Milestone is a combination of date and time in a calendar, list of results achieved 
by this date, acceptance criteria, and percentage of Budget to be paid by this date. If 
time is not defined, default time should be used, which is equal to 2:00pm EST (GMT-5). 
Milestones are attached to Specification.</milestone>

<operation>Operation is an ongoing, repetitive or one-time action or piece of work that is 
performed by the customer. Operation includes a statement of work, deadline, and acceptance 
criteria. Operations may contain many deadlines if it is repetitive (for example, 'each Friday'). 
Operations are attached to Effective Specification.</operation>

<operationsplan>Operations Plan" is a set of Operations approved by the parties.</operationsplan>

<projectmanager>Project Manager is a representative of TPC and responsible 
for overseeing all communications and project management.</projectmanager>

<quality>Quality is as a result of dividing the total number of separately identified requirements 
in Specification that have been successfully demonstrated without Defects by the total number 
of separately identified Requirements in Specification ("Requirements demonstration metrics" as defined 
in IEEE Std 730-1998).</quality>

<documentation>Project Documentation includes project, iteration and other plans, work 
breakdown structures, architecture documentation, test plans, test results, defect logs, 
user manuals, technical references, and drafts.</documentation>

<requestedchanges>Requested Changes are requests from either party for changes of the
Baseline, which should be proceed according to the contract.</requestedchanges>

<retainer>Retainer is the price a customer shall pay for Beta-Specification.</retainer>

<risk>Risk is an uncertain event or condition that, if it occurs, extends the Baseline. 
Risk includes risk trigger, contingency reserve for schedule and cost, 
contingency plan, probability, and impact on the Baseline.</risk>

<risklist>Risk List is a set of Risks approved by the parties and may also be 
referred to as "Risk Register" or "Risk Baseline".</risklist>

<rom>ROM Estimate (rough-order-of-magnitude) is a preliminary estimate of Budget for Specification, 
provided inside Preliminary Specification before Specification is created. ROM Estimate includes low 
limit (best case) and high limit (worst case) in staff-hours.</rom>

<schedule>Schedule is a set of Milestones and may also be referred to as "Schedule Baseline".</schedule>

<scheduleestimate>Schedule Estimate is a preliminary estimate of total work duration for 
Specification.  The Schedule Estimate is provided inside Preliminary Specification before the actual Specification is created. Schedule Estimate includes 
low limit (best case) and high limit (worst case) in calendar weeks.</scheduleestimate>

<scope>Scope is a set of Effective Specifications and may also be referred to as "Scope Baseline".</scope>

<specification>Specification is a description of Deliverables that may include Functional 
and Non-functional Requirements to Deliverables from user perspective ("black-box"), design constraints, 
use-cases, Glossary, and external interfaces description (including graphical user interfaces, GUI).
Wherever used, Specification means either one of the following: Effective Specification, Alpha-Specification 
or Beta-Specification. Specification is also referred to as "Software Requirements Specification 
(SRS)", "Scope Statement", or "Change Request".</specification>

<preliminaryspecification>Preliminary Specification is an approved description of Specifications including 
ROM Estimate, Retainer, Schedule Estimate, LCO Milestone, and statement of work. Preliminary 
Specification may also be referred to as "Vision" or "Preliminary Scope Statement".</preliminaryspecification>

<alphaspecification>Alpha-Specification" is a Specification which is under development by TPC and is not yet complete. </alphaspecification>

<betapecification>Beta-Specification" is a Specification which is created by 
TPC but is not yet approved by either party.</betapecification> 

<effectivespecification>Effective Specification" is a Specification under which Acceptance Statement is 
not signed and Specification is not terminated.</effectivespecification>

<acceptedspecification>Accepted Specification" is a Specification which is accepted 
by both parties with an approved Acceptance Statement.</acceptedspecification>

<tbd>TBD ("to be determined") is a mark used in Specification in order to highlight places in 
text for further development and refinement.</tbd>

<warranty>Warranty is a Defect removal service provided by TPC.</warranty>


</terms>


