<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<hideRightColumn />

<date>6/23/09</date>

<showVoting />

<title>Risk Game</title>
<label>Risk Game</label>
<intro>Learn how we optimize risk identification process using our unique Risk Game approach</intro>
<next>innovations/metrics</next>

<description>
    The described method is a risk identification scenario for software
    development projects, where the project team is multi-lingual and
    distributed, time for the risk identification meeting is limited,
    meetings are recurrent and an amount of risks required
    is bigger than a hundred.
</description>

<keywords>
    risk game,
    risk identification,
    risk management,
    distributed risk identification,
    distributed risk management,
    risk in software development
</keywords>

<text class="tex">

    \textbf{Disclaimer:} This web page contains just an abstract of a research
    report that will be presented on \href{http://seafood.inf.ethz.ch/2009/}{SEAFOOD 2009} conference
    in Zurich, Switzerland, on 3rd of July, 2009. Materials of the conference will be
    published by Springer Verlag.
        
    One of the most important ``process area'' in project management is risk
    management, which includes risk planning, risk identification,
    qualitative and quantitative analysis, risk response planning and risk monitoring. 
    The risk identification process provides 
    the material for risk analysis and risk response planning. 
    A raw list of
    risks, that shall include hundreds of them, can
    be generated by different methods, including 
        brainstorming, 
        historical records,
        checklists and templates,
        risk charting,
        objectives-based,
        scenario-based,
        taxonomy-based,
        conduct a ``pre-mortem'',
        Affinity Diagrams,
        Delphi technique,
        expert interviews,
        Nominal Group Technique, and others.
        
    Every method has its own advantages and 
    drawbacks. However, any of them
    when applied to a project with the following constraints, will fail
    to produce a required result:
         \begin{inparaenum}[\itshape a\upshape)]
         \item project team is multi-lingual and distributed (online text chats only), 
         \item risk identification meetings must take less than one hour,
         \item meetings are held regularly (every iteration), and
         \item each meeting shall produce at least a hundred risks.
         \end{inparaenum}

    Existing methods will fail in these circumstances 
    because of (most common causes):
        \begin{inparaenum}[\itshape a\upshape)]
        \item Inattention;
        \item Language barriers;
        \item Unavoidable personal criticism;
        \item Weariness after repeating meetings; and
        \item Untrained risk identifiers.
        \end{inparaenum}

    A good solution to the outlined problems could be a method that will reduce
    the amount of efforts required for risk identification, at the same time 
    increasing personnel engagement and motivation.

    \section*{Method}

        The purpose of this method is to increase the effectiveness of
        risk identification meetings in software development projects, reduce
        the time and effort required for the meetings and make the meetings possible
        to be held in online text chat form.

        The meeting facilitator prepares and presents to the meeting participants
        the list of five key project objectives and a list of risk sources (up to dozen).
        The objectives go horizontally, while risk sources vertically. The
        matrix becomes a field for the Risk Game.

        The rules of the Risk Game are:

             \begin{enumerate}
             \item Facilitator announces the next row (risk source);
             \item Everyone invents risks for the given risk source;
             \item Facilitator chooses the winner for the row;
             \item Matrix gets the name of the winner in a corresponding cell;
             \item The person who has the most cells wins the game.
             \end{enumerate}

        The meeting recorder maintains the list of all invented risks. This list is passed
        to the facilitator by the end of the meeting. 
        The result of the Risk Game is a long list of raw unsorted risks, which will
        be used by the project management for quantitative and qualitative risk analysis.

        The proposed method is more effective than other existing methods when
        meeting time is limited (less than one hour) and 
        a big list of risks is required (more than a hundred).
        The method is more effective in such circumstances 
        because it quickly involves everybody in the process, 
        converts individual criticism into a fair competition and 
        stimulates group thinking.

</text>

</article>


