<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>9/12/08</date>

<label>Continuous Integration</label>
<title>
    TechnoPark Corp. Stays on Track with Continuous Integration
</title>

<keywords>
    continuous integration, automated building, integration,
    continuous integration software
</keywords>

<description>
    TechnoPark Corp. uses Apache Continuum for continuous integration of their projects
</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL, September 10, 2008 - TechnoPark Corp. uses one of the
    best available Open-Source solutions for their continuous integration needs.  Apache Continuum
    version 1.2 allows TechnoPark Corp. to keep an eye on the details of
    intricate coding within the projects TechnoPark Corp. manages.</p>

    <p>Continuous integration helps TechnoPark Corp. to be more efficient
    with their time when it comes to coding.  When developers have an early
    warning system to detect faulty code, they spend less time trouble shooting
    and more time creating useful solutions for their clients.</p>

    <p>Apache Continuum helps developers and teams to improve and maintain quality
    when they build their project.  Apache Continuum notifies developers when they
    have created incompatible code or if something they built is broken.</p>

    <p>Continuous integration is an automated system that monitors code for
    errors.  One of the advantages of an automated system is that it requires
    its user to be organized.  The system uses a developer's records and
    processes to monitor the creation of code.  If a developer inputs the
    wrong information, the automated system won't work.</p>

    <p>This is useful because when a developer is creating large quantities of
    code, they could be unaware of a small error that will disable the
    whole project.  Without an automated system, a project could be near
    completion before bugs were discovered.  With continuous integration, small
    errors are caught early at a point when they are easier to correct.  This
    also saves the time of having to hunt for tiny problems in vast amounts of code.</p>

    <p>Authors Martin Fowler and Kent Beck first wrote about continuous
    integration for the programming community in the late 1990's.  One
    continuous integration provider, CruiseControl, now employs Martin Fowler
    through its parent company, Thoughtworks.</p>

    <p>Appache Continuum can be found at
    [http://continuum.apache.org/](http://continuum.apache.org/)</p>

</text>
</article>
