<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>3/20/08</date>

<label>Video On Demand</label>
<title>TechnoPark Corp. Helps Deliver "Video on Demand" over the Internet.</title>     

<description>TechnoPark Corp. will Create Customizable Platform Software for IPTV Translations.</description>

<text>

<p>Naples, FL, March 19, 2008 - TechnoPark Corp. announces it will create 
customizable platform software for IPTV translations.  This software will allow their 
South American client to deliver video over the Internet.</p>

<p>Over the next five months, TechnoPark Corp. will act as project 
managers, system analyzers, and development architects for the Video on Demand 
(VoD) system scheduled to handle almost unlimited amount of simultaneous customers.</p>

<p>"As software developers, IPTV's market niche has great potential for 
us," says Arthur Petrenko, Marketing Director of TechnoPark Corp. "We believe 
that TV and movies over the Internet will replace DVD's very soon. Our company 
is going to get valuable experience in this niche."</p>

<p>TechnoPark's client, the South America VoD provider, will connect
customers to over 10 thousand films and TV channels. With TechnoPark's 
customizable platform software system, publishers, moviemakers and online TV companies 
will have the ability to deliver video, films, TV channels, cartoons, and 
many other media formats through the Internet.  It will also enable the South America client 
to create a pay-per-view or pay per month business model.</p>

<p>TechnoPark Corp. will release the first version of the IPTV software platform 
in June of 2008.  At this time, the name of the client, and more details 
on the features of the TechnoPark Corp. software, will be available.</p>

</text>
</article>