<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>1/11/08</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. Provides Proof of Privacy</title>

<description>TechnoPark Corp. displays the TRUSTe  Seal of privacy and works toward ISO 27001 certification.</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL, January 11, 2008 -  TechnoPark Corp. (TPC) has enlisted a third
    party verification for their security and privacy practices.  By displaying the
    TRUSTe seal, along with the TPC privacy policy, TechnoPark Corp. verifies that
    they meet industry standards for protecting their customer's rights and their customer's
    personal information.</p>

    <p>A privacy policy states the legal ways a company collects and distributes personal
    information.  For their provider of a Privacy Seal, TechnoPark Corp. chose TRUSTe,
    an internationally recognized non-profit organization that verifies a company's
    privacy standards.  Along with verifying TechnoPark Corp.'s privacy statement,
    TRUSTe provides dispute resolution programs and they regularly review their customer's
    websites for continued compliance.</p>

    <p>"TechnoPark Corp always strives for transparency," says Arthur Petrenko,
    Marketing Director for TechnoPark Corp.  "We want to be sure that when a
    prospective customer considers using our services they are absolutely confident
    that their personal data will never be compromised."</p>

    <p>In order to receive a privacy seal, TPC had to show that their customers can
    opt out of direct marketing and the selling of their information to third parties.
    The privacy policy explains such things as why TPC collects personal information,
    how they use the information they collect, and how to unsubscribe from email
    notifications. The complete privacy policy and seal can be found at
    [http://www.technoparkcorp.com/about/privacypolicy]({% href about/privacypolicy %}).</p>

    <p>To take their privacy assurances even further, TechnoPark Corp. is
    also now preparing for ISO 27001 certification.  This is a three-step process that
    verifies security procedures, audits information security controls, and then
    provides a follow-up inspection to assure that a company maintains compliance.
    TechnoPark Corp. expects to be certified in the next eight to ten months.  This
    process follows on the heels of their successful ISO 9001:2000 certification
    in November of 2007.</p>

    <p>More information about TRUSTe can be found on their website,
    <ahref name="http://www.truste.org">www.truste.org</ahref>.  TechnoPark Corp. is
    a US-based outsourcing software development company with a development center in
    the Ukraine.</p>

</text>
</article>
