<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<invisible/>
<title>Legal Notes and Terms of Use</title>
<label>Legal Notes</label>
<intro>Read official legal notes about trademarks and service marks used online</intro>
<next>about/privacypolicy</next>

<keywords>
    Legal information,
    trademarks,
    registered marks,
    custom software,
    terms of use
</keywords>

<description>
    The trademarks used on our site are registered and respected
    marks of their owners. Terms of use of the site are declared here.
</description>

<text>

    <p>The following are terms of a legal agreement between you and TechnoPark Corp.
    By accessing, browsing, or using this web-site, you acknowledge that you 
    have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these terms and to 
    comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including export and 
    re-export control laws and regulations.</p> 

    <p>If you do not agree to these 
    terms, please do not use this web-site.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. may, without notice to you, at any time revise these 
    Legal Notes and any other information contained in this web-site by 
    updating this posting.</p> 

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. may also make improvements or 
    changes in the products, services, or programs described in this web-site 
    at any time without notice.</p>           

    <h1>General Notes</h1>

        <p>This web-site contains proprietary notices and copyright information, 
        the terms of which must be observed and followed. Please see the section 
        entitled 'Trademarks' for related information.</p>

        <p>This web-site and all content in this web-site may not be copied, 
        reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, distributed, 
        or used for the creation of derivative works without TechnoPark Corp.'s 
        prior written consent, except that TechnoPark Corp. grants you 
        non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited permission to access and display 
        the web-pages within this web-site, solely on your computer and for 
        your personal, non-commercial use of this web-site.</p> 

        <p>This permission is 
        conditioned on your not modifying the content displayed on this web-site, 
        your keeping intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices, 
        and your acceptance of any terms, conditions, and notices accompanying the 
        content or otherwise set forth in this web-site. </p>

        <p>Notwithstanding the 
        foregoing, any software and other materials that are made available for 
        downloading, access, or other use from this web-site with their own license 
        terms, conditions, and notices will be governed by such terms, conditions, and notices.</p>

        <p>Your failure to comply with the terms, conditions, and notices on this 
        web-site will result in automatic termination of any rights granted to you, 
        without prior notice, and you must immediately destroy all copies of 
        downloaded materials in your possession or control. </p>

        <p>Except for the 
        limited permission in the preceding paragraphs, TechnoPark Corp. does not grant 
        you any express or implied rights or licenses under any patents, trademarks, 
        copyrights, or other proprietary or intellectual property rights. You may not 
        mirror any of the content from this web-site on another web-site or in 
        any other media.</p>

    <h1>Disclaimers</h1>

        <p>Information on this web-site is not promised or guaranteed to be correct, 
        current, or complete, and this web-site may contain technical inaccuracies 
        or typographical errors. TechnoPark Corp. assumes no responsibility 
        (and expressly disclaims responsibility) for updating this web-site to 
        keep information current or to ensure the accuracy or completeness of any 
        posted information. </p>

        <p>Accordingly, you should confirm the accuracy and completeness of all posted 
        information before making any decision related to any services, products, 
        or other matters described in this web-site.</p>

        <p>TechnoPark Corp. provides no assurances that any reported problems will 
        be resolved by TechnoPark Corp., even if TechnoPark Corp. elects to provide 
        information with the goal of addressing a problem.</p>

    <h1>Trademarks</h1>

        <png style="float: left;">//images/logo</png>

        <p>The trademark (nine-circles logo and "<b>Plan Your Success</b>" slogan) is a trademark
        of TechnoPark Corp., registered on 4-Nov-08 in United States Patent and Trademark
        Office (<a href="http://www.uspto.gov">USPTO</a>), 
        <a href="http://tarr.uspto.gov/servlet/tarr?regser=serial&amp;entry=77438094">see details</a>.
        Any oppositions you may send directly to USPTO or to <a href="${mailto:pr}">copyright</a> department
        of TechnoPark Corp by email. You can download our logo in <a href="${def:Site::BuildImage(false, '/logo.svg')}">SVG format</a>.</p>

        <p>The product names used in this website are for identification purposes only. 
        All trademarks and registered trademarks are the property of their respective owners.</p>

    <h1>Third-Parties</h1>

        <p>This web-site may provide links or references to non-TechnoPark Corp. 
        web-sites and resources. TechnoPark Corp. makes no representations, warranties, 
        or other commitments whatsoever about any non-TechnoPark Corp. web-sites or 
        third-party resources that may be referenced, accessible from, or linked 
        to any TechnoPark Corp. web-site. </p>

        <p>A link to a non-TechnoPark Corp. web-site does not mean that TechnoPark Corp. 
        endorses the content or use of such web-site or its owner. </p>

        <p>In addition, TechnoPark Corp. is not a party to or responsible for any 
        transactions you may enter into with third parties, even if you learn of 
        such parties (or use a link to such parties) from an TechnoPark Corp. 
        web-site. </p>

        <p>Accordingly, you acknowledge and agree that TechnoPark Corp. is not responsible 
        for the availability of such external web-sites or resources, and is 
        not responsible or liable for any content, services, products, or other 
        materials on or available from those web-sites or resources.</p>

        <p>When you access a non-TechnoPark Corp. web-site, even one that may contain the 
        TechnoPark Corp. logo, please understand that it is independent from 
        TechnoPark Corp., and that TechnoPark Corp. does not control the content on 
        that web-site. </p>

        <p>It is up to you to take precautions to protect yourself from viruses, worms, 
        trojan horses, and other potentially destructive programs, and to protect your 
        information as you deem appropriate.</p>

    <h1>Linking to this web-site</h1>

        <p>All links to this web-site must be approved in writing by TechnoPark Corp., 
        except that TechnoPark Corp. consents to links in which the link and the 
        pages that are activated by the link do not: (a) create frames around 
        any page on this web-site or use other techniques that alter in any 
        way the visual presentation or appearance of any content within this 
        web-site; (b) misrepresent your relationship with TechnoPark Corp.; (c) imply 
        that TechnoPark Corp. approves or endorses you, your web-site, or 
        your service or product offerings; and (d) present false or misleading impressions 
        about TechnoPark Corp. or otherwise damage the goodwill associated with the 
        TechnoPark Corp. name or trademarks.</p> 

        <p>As a further condition to being permitted to link to this web-site, you 
        agree that TechnoPark Corp. may at any time, in its sole discretion, 
        terminate permission to link to this web-site.</p> 

        <p>In such event, you agree to immediately remove all links to this web-site 
        and to cease using any TechnoPark Corp. trademark.</p>

    <h1>Translations</h1>

        <p>Certain text in this web-site may be made available in languages other than English. 
        Text may be translated by a person or solely by computer software with no 
        human intervention or review.</p> 

        <p>These translations are provided as a convenience to you, and TechnoPark Corp. 
        makes no representations or commitments regarding the accuracy or completeness of 
        the translation, whether or not computer-generated or performed by a person. 
        Please see the below Disclaimer of Warranty for additional conditions.</p>

    <h1>Disclaimer of Warranty</h1>

        <p>Use of this web-site is at your sole risk. All materials, information, 
        products, software, programs, and services are provided "as is," with no warranties 
        or guarantees whatsoever. TechnoPark Corp. expressly disclaims to the 
        fullest extent permitted by law all express, implied, statutory, and 
        other warranties, guarantees, or representations, including, without 
        limitation, the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, 
        and non-infringement of proprietary and intellectual property rights.</p> 

        <p>Without limitation, TechnoPark Corp. makes no warranty or guarantee that 
        this web-site will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free.</p>

        <p>You understand and agree that if you download or otherwise obtain materials, 
        information, products, software, programs, or services, you do so at 
        your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible 
        for any damages that may result, including loss of data or damage to 
        your computer system.</p>

        <p>Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of warranties, so the 
        above exclusions may not apply to you.</p>

    <h1>Limitation of Liability</h1>

        <p>In no event will TechnoPark Corp. be liable to any party for any direct, 
        indirect, incidental, special, exemplary or consequential damages of 
        any type whatsoever related to or arising from this web-site or 
        any use of this web-site, or of any web-site or resource linked to, 
        referenced, or accessed through this web-site, or for the use or 
        downloading of, or access to, any materials, information, products, 
        or services, including, without limitation, any lost profits, business 
        interruption, lost savings or loss of programs or other data, even if 
        TechnoPark Corp. is expressly advised of the possibility of such damages.</p> 

        <p>This exclusion and waiver of liability applies to all causes of action, 
        whether based on contract, warranty, tort, or any other legal theories.</p>

        <p>Additional or different terms, conditions, and notices may apply to 
        specific materials, information, products, software, and services offered 
        through this web-site.</p> 

        <p>In the event of any conflict, such additional or different terms, conditions, 
        and notices will prevail over these legal notes. please see the 
        applicable agreement or notice.</p>

</text>

<images>
    <logo>
MB5!.1PT*&amp;@H````-24A$4@```(L```!4&quot;`,```&quot;%KS0W````&quot;7!(67,```L3
M```+$P$`FIP8```*3VE#0U!0:&amp;]T;W-H;W`@24-#(&#039;!R;V9I;&amp;4``&#039;C:G5-G
M5%/I%CWWWO1&quot;2XB`E$MO4A4((%)&quot;BX`4D28J(0D02H@AH=D54&lt;$1144$&amp;\B@
MB`..CH&quot;,%5$L#(H*V`?D(:*.@Z.(BLK[X7NC:]:\]^;-_K77/N&gt;L\YVSSP?`
M&quot;`R62#-1-8`,J4(&gt;$&gt;&quot;#Q\3&amp;X&gt;0N0($*)&#039;``$`BS9&quot;%S_2,!`/A^/#PK(L`&#039;
MO@`!&gt;-,+&quot;`#`39O`,!R&#039;_P_J0IE&lt;`8&quot;$`&lt;!TD3A+&quot;(`4`$!ZCD*F`$!&amp;`8&quot;=
MF&quot;93`*`$`&amp;#+8V+C`%`M`&amp;`G?^;3`(&quot;=^)E[`0!;E&quot;$5`:&quot;1`&quot;`398A$`&amp;@[
M`*S/5HI%`%@P`!1F2\0Y`-@M`#!)5V9(`+&quot;W`,#.$`NR``@,`#!1B(4I``1[
M`&amp;#((R-X`(29`!1&amp;\E&lt;\\2NN$.&lt;J``!XF;(\N20Y18%;&quot;&quot;UQ!U=7+AXHSDD7
M*Q0V80)AFD`NPGF9&amp;3*!-`_@\\P``*&quot;1%1&#039;@@_/]&gt;,X.KL[.-HZV#E\MZK\&amp;
M_R)B8N/^Y&lt;^K&lt;$```.%T?M&#039;^+&quot;^S&amp;H`[!H!M_J(E[@1H7@N@=?&gt;+9K(/0+4`
MH.G:5_-P^&#039;X\/$6AD+G9V&gt;7DY-A*Q$);8&lt;I7??YGPE_`5_UL^7X\_/?UX+[B
M)($R78%&#039;!/C@PLST3*4&lt;SY()A&amp;+&lt;YH]&#039;_+&lt;+__P=TR+$26*Y6&quot;H4XU$2&lt;8Y$
MFHSS,J4BB4*2*&lt;4ETO]DXM\L^P,^WS4`L&amp;H^`7N1+:A=8P/V2R&lt;06&#039;3`XO&lt;`
M`/*[;\&#039;4*`@#@&amp;B#X&lt;]W_^\__4&gt;@)0&quot;`9DF2&lt;0``7D0D+E3*LS_&#039;&quot;```1*&quot;!
M*K!!&amp;_3!&amp;&quot;S`!AS!!=S!&quot;_Q@-H1&quot;),3&quot;0A!&quot;&quot;F2`&#039;&#039;)@*:R&quot;0BB&amp;S;`=*F`O
MU$`=-,!1:(:3&lt;`XNPE6X#CUP#_IA&quot;)[!*+R!&quot;01!R`@382&#039;:B`%BBE@CC@@7
MF87X(&lt;%(!!*+)&quot;#)B!11(DN1-4@Q4HI4(%5(&#039;?(]&lt;@(YAUQ&amp;NI$[R``R@OR&amp;
MO$&lt;QE(&amp;R43W4#+5#N:@W&amp;H1&amp;H@O09&#039;0QFH\6H)O0&lt;K0:/8PVH&gt;?0JV@/VH\^
M0\&lt;PP.@8!S/$;#`NQL-&quot;L3@L&quot;9-CR[$BK`RKQAJP5JP#NXGU8\^Q=P02@47`
M&quot;38$=T(@81Y!2%A,6$[82*@@&#039;&quot;0T$=H)-PD#A%&#039;&quot;)R*3J$NT)KH1^&lt;088C(Q
MAUA(+&quot;/6$H\3+Q![B$/$-R02B4,R)[F0`DFQI%32$M)&amp;TFY2(^DLJ9LT2!HC
MD\G:9&amp;NR!SF4+&quot;`KR(7DG&gt;3#Y#/D&amp;^0A\EL*G6)`&lt;:3X4^(H4LIJ2AGE$.4T
MY09EF#)!5:.:4MVHH501-8]:0JVAME*O48&gt;H$S1UFCG-@Q9)2Z6MHI73&amp;F@7
M:/=IK^ATNA&#039;=E1Y.E]!7TLOI1^B7Z`/T=PP-AA6#QXAG*!F;&amp;`&lt;89QEW&amp;*^8
M3*89TXL9QU0P-S&#039;KF.&gt;9#YEO55@JMBI\%9&#039;*&quot;I5*E2:5&amp;RHO5*FJIJK&gt;J@M5
M\U7+5(^I7E-]KD95,U/CJ0G4EJM5JIU0ZU,;4V&gt;I.ZB&#039;JF&gt;H;U0_I&#039;Y9_8D&amp;
M6&lt;-,PT]#I%&amp;@L5_CO,8@&quot;V,9LW@L(6L-JX9U@37$)K&#039;-V7QV*KN8_1V[BSVJ
MJ:$Y0S-*,U&gt;S4O.49C\&#039;XYAQ^)QT3@GG**&gt;7\WZ*WA3O*&gt;(I&amp;Z8T3+DQ95QK
MJI:7EEBK2*M1JT?KO3:N[:&gt;=IKU%NUG[@0Y!QTHG7&quot;=&#039;9X_.!9WG4]E3W:&lt;*
MIQ9-/3KUKBZJ:Z4;H;M$=[]NI^Z8GKY&gt;@)Y,;Z?&gt;&gt;;WG^AQ]+_U4_6WZI_5&#039;
M#%@&amp;LPPD!ML,SA@\Q35Q;SP=+\?;\5%#7&lt;-`0Z5AE6&amp;7X821N=$\H]5&amp;C48/
MC&amp;G&amp;7.,DXVW&amp;;&lt;:C)@8F(29+3&gt;I-[II23;FF*:8[3#M,Q\W,S:+-UIDUFSTQ
MUS+GF^&gt;;UYO?MV!:&gt;%HLMJBVN&amp;5)LN1:IEGNMKQNA5HY6:5855I=LT:MG:TE
MUKNMNZ&lt;1I[E.DTZKGM9GP[#QMLFVJ;&lt;9L.78!MNNMFVV?6%G8A=GM\6NP^Z3
MO9-]NGV-_3T&#039;#8?9#JL=6AU^&lt;[1R%#I6.MZ:SISN/WW%]);I+V=8SQ#/V#/C
MMA/+*&lt;1IG5.;TT=G%V&gt;Y&lt;X/SB(N)2X+++I&lt;^+IL;QMW(O&gt;1*=/5Q7&gt;%ZTO6=
MF[.;PNVHVZ_N-NYI[H?&lt;G\PTGRF&gt;63-ST,/(0^!1Y=$_&quot;Y^5,&amp;O?K&#039;Y/0T^!
M9[7G(R]C+Y%7K=&gt;PMZ5WJO=A[Q&lt;^]CYRG^,^XSPWWC+&gt;65_,-\&quot;WR+?+3\-O
MGE^%WT-_(_]D_WK_T0&quot;G@&quot;4!9P.)@4&amp;!6P+[^&#039;I\(;^./SK;9?:RV&gt;U!C*&quot;Y
M015!CX*M@N7!K2%HR.R0K2&#039;WYYC.D&lt;YI#H50?NC6T`=AYF&amp;+PWX,)X6&#039;A5&gt;&amp;
M/XYPB%@:T3&amp;7-7?1W$-SWT3Z1)9$WIMG,4\YKRU*-2H^JBYJ/-HWNC2Z/\8N
M9EG,U5B=6$EL2QPY+BJN-FYLOM_\[?.&#039;XIWB&quot;^-[%Y@OR%UP&gt;:&#039;.PO2%IQ:I
M+A(L.I9`3(A..)3P01`JJ!:,)?(3=R6.&quot;GG&quot;&#039;&lt;)G(B_1-M&amp;(V$-&lt;*AY.\D@J
M37J2[)&amp;\-7DDQ3.E+.6YA&quot;&gt;ID+Q,#4S=FSJ&gt;%IIV(&amp;TR/3J],8.2D9!Q0JHA
M39.V9^IGYF9VRZQEA;+^Q6Z+MR\&gt;E0?):[.0K`59+0JV0J;H5%HHURH&#039;LF=E
M5V:_S8G*.9:KGBO-[&lt;RSRMN0-YSOG__M$L(2X9*VI89+5RT=6.:]K&amp;HYLCQQ
M&gt;=L*XQ4%*X96!JP\N(JV*FW53ZOM5Y&gt;N?KTF&gt;DUK@5[!RH+!M0%KZPM5&quot;N6%
M?&gt;O&lt;U^U=3U@O6=^U8?J&amp;G1L^%8F*KA3;%Y&lt;5?]@HW&#039;CE&amp;X=ORK^9W)2TJ:O$
MN63/9M)FZ&gt;;&gt;+9Y;#I:JE^:7#FX-V=JT#=]6M.WU]D7;+Y?-*-N[@[9#N:._
M/+B\9:?)SLT[/U2D5/14^E0V[M+=M6&#039;7^&amp;[1[AM[O/8T[-7;6[SW_3[)OMM5
M`55-U6;59?M)^[/W/ZZ)JNGXEOMM7:U.;7&#039;MQP/2`_T&#039;(PZVU[G4U1W2/512
MC]8KZT&lt;.QQ^^_IWO=RT--@U5C9S&amp;XB-P1&#039;GDZ?&lt;)W_&lt;&gt;#3K:=HQ[K.$&#039;TQ]V
M&#039;6&lt;=+VI&quot;FO*:1IM3FOM;8ENZ3\P^T=;JWGK\1]L?#YPT/%EY2O-4R6G:Z8+3
MDV?RSXR=E9U]?B[YW&amp;#;HK9[YV/.WVH/;^^Z$&#039;3ATD7_B^&lt;[O#O.7/*X=/*R
MV^435[A7FJ\Z7VWJ=.H\_I/33\&gt;[G+N:KKE&lt;:[GN&gt;KVU&gt;V;WZ1N&gt;-\[=]+UY
M\1;_UM6&gt;.3W=O?-Z;_?%]_7?%MU^&lt;B?]SLN[V7&lt;G[JV\3[Q?]$#M0=E#W8?5
M/UO^W-COW&#039;]JP&#039;&gt;@\]&#039;&lt;1_&lt;&amp;A8//_I&#039;UCP]#!8^9C\N&amp;#8;KGC@^.3GB/W+]
MZ?RG0\]DSR:&gt;%_ZB_LNN%Q8O?OC5Z]?.T9C1H9?REY._;7RE_&gt;K`ZQFOV\;&quot;
MQAZ^R7@S,5[T5OOMP7?&lt;=QWOH]\/3^1\(&#039;\H_VCYL?53T*?[DQF3D_\$`YCS
M_&amp;,S+=L````@8TA230``&gt;B4``(&quot;#``#Y_P``@.D``&#039;4P``#J8```.I@``!=O
MDE_%1@```P!03%1%35QEB)*8(30_\/&#039;RQ,G,0*[&lt;TM;8IJVR:WA_?\GGX&gt;3E
MEZ&quot;E7&amp;IR/T]9M;N_O^3S&gt;H6,,$%,&lt;,+EW_&#039;Y,*?98+SBG];MS^OVK]WP$)K3
M[_C\C]#J(*&#039;64+7?____`)/0$B8R_/[\````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````.Y45J```!N))1$%4&gt;-KLFFMWHM@2AA\N*N(]]HH&amp;
M6T+^_X]J@]&#039;$&#039;$V\@B*7^8`HMYYV$IV362M\R)(*XDOMVE5/[8WPP)&lt;YA&amp;\M
MU]1B&quot;E#LI(Q#$&#039;LIV\B&#039;_C6U#%T#8.%L]:-MXG&lt;!S+ISDFCZ@@[PXO:OI,4L
M_X@^+C:1&#039;P;WQW\7M,.GV?HH==[*N9&#039;4^K04]2@%Y7U3!^#YY]&#039;6J#W7`!C?
M-DX7OM2R=Q(_[99R.W:BNR;`:S=^Q=T08&#039;07MW4&#039;5]`R_)$XU0N`:2&gt;OJ0$X
M2=O]Y/):E-1YUP1%3]H:,Q@9J0OMRVOYD3948)/S*_NTK7IQ+&lt;.,905I%S&quot;&#039;
M(&amp;UK7R%V+W=\)2V?S2^+1MIBUYBI*=NVE@WRA7)IO^BSS-.!E+8%X&#039;/]&gt;91*
M&amp;TP[69NI07N1,OJ7UZ+-LMHZ\U1J!O&quot;2MI?&gt;%6)W9\;/GGL`JX3`EUN`]DO&lt;
M-MM?I4Z/*J?X?3[49-,[Y9B7J!&quot;]-T]2+/TZ_!)A&quot;5/_Q&quot;IC-50XL_MISF&#039;A
MW%Z1ZX8&gt;%*4DV(T*%NH^&amp;183ST&#039;=];_9^U_78OK5-BQL/SX@XYT!IBK&amp;:^#,
MMW08E%S]6EI&gt;[&gt;C6T^.G82V:7+-=I&#039;!B19/+K+:OH^4Y!I317!W&#039;@-*40S&amp;C
MN#&gt;BR7_97#&gt;(LVT[K(K#NP0#3P#,Q,#&lt;S:Z@97*?)*3!$7!/8BR`0C)&amp;UN;E
MM:1+G`&quot;,4R!AC&amp;#2315XY?IU6A]&quot;(7W1/M28.#87US+*S$X/K!Q^R6@Q+J[%
MSP6L&#039;-OZO\6[G]52S%A46.3T0IE0O?P\ZBQRXM3.B9&lt;@1_.EQRB%D\QZX*8O
MVH)K_O&amp;7/ZU%-+/YI9]:1&#039;C404\Y9G&quot;%OE%/]L4O;0`U(7`F`AB)K&amp;\6KS&amp;/
MVL]Q*6$AZLAFMEY:LVR]_&#039;.=7JS@1CT_WSE&amp;&gt;CD,LQ#E_$?QF&amp;X&amp;!RY.@/$?
MM/C`_.:?9-]]`$T_$0(305BC2-MXXC-E84LU&quot;#IG&lt;]U;\Y]JN5ZNJWX9WMVL
M7`VPUJ!**^BR#%90\R)&#039;6&lt;L?+X`&lt;@X`W:05-02[%Q\@.H!HDQT@1UB&quot;4SQVC
MIQ/]S2T-Q,6!C&#039;RO!&quot;R76MJEEE&lt;Y\(-XG*FG1=_YZA2[$7&lt;-U,Z&#039;ZM%3!&amp;GB
M&#039;K&quot;*&amp;5#=*)6H.,E1-1X%QW6\9I1LS.D1`8WMZ,PQNB4:H]`&#039;&amp;QFW`K!5654`
M7HN4%X&lt;QLN,#@U4%F&quot;1&amp;YI!@IFW^/L&#039;(&amp;4NEX@,X76`95K8R.Z&lt;([-E4`&#039;;=
M:&quot;$#=DE(4NTR8&quot;5`J2TE!N@W:TAGY=UQ&#039;4HRP(H2P*8&lt;^^][,?MPPQ2S-2?A
M3DI&quot;X/@C6F2`*8`65N`$J:9+G&amp;3E.%L`.0U[A0_7HT8,G&gt;(=QU+*D5[.T9+A
M7&gt;O#6NS8]W&lt;QNYMSI;?(@=WMGZ&#039;X\KQK(^G7Y=UJC`OC0Z#DKCM\K+&quot;&lt;J^7M
MT/I`$JU5)X?&amp;U9QXR?#NX,-:W#!0QI#:&amp;DD&#039;C&#039;&gt;3LR=2SM%2^J@62PO[51E`
M7/Y-LQ8`6BIXIQWHO*1XS3U?B\1NLXD&gt;ZJT`,+XY&gt;%]X.^9DZJ_)&quot;E(,DV)R
MV0I@GXPB3S^+I591K7MUXX70&lt;&gt;K1NG&#039;B,=9J7$KILFM!&lt;JZC-GX=Z*ZR,\0]
MQJ]UD(+V=!RF050%&gt;\HQ7!=/VKF\:[L5P)FJ5O053]A%SGHKEB2`\6G;=R&gt;\
M:K#QA7J\C!4LG86=V!8?RN4&amp;IKK7/K&quot;.^:21WN#]PKW]MY;_1Q^0;B!I5;Z$
MEJ_DEV\MF6/B]OYM+=E\_PNJ3@\[R%W=D/O,EFKG-W&lt;S&quot;UL$XW)SVE#D[.+:
MX&gt;CA@J3\3@KE0KU&gt;NZ!?V!FF_G1HSU&amp;W.D-*5BWL/&gt;2?0VDOP*M%N&lt;/$-AAZ
M!D-)#BOZNMD&quot;&amp;*,Q]OHP=BCTF-BHMYB*I=[&quot;:$^A=_A[3JX3#F:YA%T#S]^4
M;L(^KS]UU4#GETUU:^+&lt;@W&lt;/WETQ9.!F&lt;V`&quot;NQWL/&#039;C&gt;-QH*HVU``501&gt;P!N
MI:%@NI7&amp;6?OVS5\_#YOJ;5&#039;RYT#CX6YV8`7?P&amp;!DB(:5P.YE^(I&amp;ZU$(3OW@
MI%MMM=H4_0&gt;CQ;`M2/4FZ)M5&amp;TD/6OUSM+R7(A(:WX8@^&#039;XBM&lt;Y@#CY]=#_6
M;,TB2C+NBR&gt;*&lt;L*F&lt;BV$&gt;+MTY^_P+`0S&gt;H_V?&#039;2.%D&amp;+1G+_^&quot;#DA]D04U2!
M4=A0KA)M`$IX8Y&#039;9$8&amp;1D!X&gt;&#039;D`3U&quot;48PGOQ3(:+&amp;E=W(.1-[?ZT-@C$+?W&#039;
M2NR]`&amp;`J+83E`X&#039;Q/C&lt;&gt;Z?T21?QV_&gt;9_FT:K/54&#039;%#6SX`M5)K[?LL_0\AAV
MR)($&amp;[%47(4?2]%K&amp;B4/L)2@Z71`WN_?5@92U%0[0B78@O:ZJ3Q+(&quot;ESQ:&lt;]
ME&quot;M[L/R@N89=(*W8U;;._KL&gt;_0&gt;U?/[=T,L=?PT`I.1KCT&#039;8+%8`````245.
%1*Y&quot;8((`
`
    </logo>
</images>

</article>




