<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<invisible/>

<title>Password Policy</title>
<label>Password Policy</label>
<intro>Review good security practices in the selection and use of passwords</intro>
<next>about/legalnotes</next>

<text>

    <p>Passwords are an important aspect of computer security. They are the front 
    line of protection for user accounts. A poorly chosen password may result 
    in the compromise of TechnoPark Corp.'s entire corporate network. As such, 
    all TechnoPark Corp. employees (including contractors and vendors with access to
    TechnoPark Corp. systems) are responsible for taking the appropriate steps, as 
    outlined below, to select and secure their passwords.</p>

    <h2>Purpose</h2>
    
    <p>The purpose of this policy is to establish a standard for creation of strong 
    passwords, the protection of those passwords, and the frequency of change.</p>

    <h2>Scope</h2>
    
    <p>The scope of this policy includes all personnel who have or are responsible for 
    an account (or any form of access that supports or requires a password) on 
    any system that resides at any TechnoPark Corp. facility, has access to the 
    TechnoPark Corp. network, or stores any non-public TechnoPark Corp. information.</p>

    <h2>Policy</h2>
    
    <p>All system-level passwords (e.g., root, enable, NT admin, application 
    administration accounts, etc.) must be changed on at least a quarterly basis.</p>

    <p>All production system-level passwords must be part of the TechnoPark Corp. 
     administered global password management database.</p>

    <p>All user-level passwords (e.g., email, web, desktop computer, etc.) must be 
    changed at least every six months. The recommended change interval is every four months.</p>

    <p>User accounts that have system-level privileges granted through group memberships 
    or programs such as "sudo" must have a unique password from all other accounts held by that user.</p>

    <p>Passwords must not be inserted into email messages or other forms of electronic communication.</p>

    <p>Where SNMP is used, the community strings must be defined as something other than the
    standard defaults of "public," "private" and "system" and must be different from the passwords
    used to log in interactively. A keyed hash must be used where available (e.g., SNMPv2).</p>

    <p>All user-level and system-level passwords must conform to the guidelines described below.</p>

    <h2>Password Construction Guidelines</h2>

    <p>Passwords are used for various purposes at TechnoPark Corp.. Some of the more common uses include:
    user level accounts, web accounts, email accounts, screen saver protection, voicemail password, and local
    router logins. Since very few systems have support for one-time tokens (i.e., dynamic passwords which are
    only used once), everyone should be aware of how to select strong passwords.</p>

    <p>Poor, weak passwords have the following characteristics:</p>

    <ul>
    
        <li>The password contains less than eight characters</li>
    
        <li>The password is a word found in a dictionary (English or foreign)</li>
    
        <li>The pasword is a common usage word such as: names of family, pets, friends, 
        co-workers, fantasy characters, etc., computer terms and names, commands, 
        sites, companies, hardware, software, birthdays and other personal information such 
        as addresses and phone numbers, word or number patterns like aaabbb, qwerty, zyxwvuts, 123321, etc.,</li>

    </ul>                                                    

    <p>Strong passwords have the following characteristics:</p>

    <ul>
        <li>Contain both upper and lower case characters (e.g., a-z, A-Z)</li>
        
        <li>Have digits and punctuation characters as well as letters e.g., 0-9, !@#$%^&amp;*()_+|~-=\`{}[]:";'&lt;&gt;?,./)</li>
        
        <li>Are at least eight alphanumeric characters long and is a passphrase (e.g. Ohmy1stubbedmyt0e).</li>

        <li>Are not a word in any language, slang, dialect, jargon, etc.</li>
        
        <li>Are not based on personal information, names of family, etc.</li>
        
        <li>Passwords should never be written down or stored on-line. Try to create passwords that can be
        easily remembered. One way to do this is create a password based on a song title, affirmation, or
        other phrase. For example, the phrase might be: "This May Be One Way To Remember" and the
        password could be: &quot;TmB1w2R!&quot; or &quot;Tmb1W&gt;r~&quot; or some other variation.</li>

    </ul>    

    <p>NOTE: Do not use either of these examples as passwords!</p>

    <h2>Password Protection Standards</h2>

    <p>Do not use the same password for TechnoPark Corp. accounts as for other 
    non-TechnoPark Corp. access (e.g., personal ISP account, option trading, 
    benefits, etc.). Where possible, don't use the same password for various 
    TechnoPark Corp. access needs. For example, select one password for the Panel
    systems and a separate password for test deployment systems. Also, 
    select a separate password to be used for an NT account and a UNIX account.</p>

    <p>Do not share TechnoPark Corp. passwords with anyone, including administrative 
    assistants or secretaries.</p>

    <p>All passwords are to be treated as sensitive, confidential TechnoPark Corp. information.</p>

    <p>Here is a list of "dont's":</p>

    <ul>
        <li>Don't reveal a password over the phone to ANYONE</li>
        <li>Don't reveal a password in an email message</li>
        <li>Don't reveal a password to the boss</li>
        <li>Don't talk about a password in front of others</li>
        <li>Don't hint at the format of a password (e.g., "my family name")</li>
        <li>Don't reveal a password on questionnaires or security forms</li>
        <li>Don't share a password with family members</li>
        <li>Don't reveal a password to co-workers while on vacation</li>
    </ul>    

    <p>If someone demands a password, refer them to this document or have them 
    call Chief Security Officer (CSO).</p>

    <p>Again, do not write passwords down and store them anywhere in your 
    office. Do not store passwords in a file on ANY computer system 
    (including Palm Pilots or similar devices) without encryption.</p>

    <p>Change passwords at least once every six months (except system-level 
    passwords which must be changed quarterly). The recommended change interval 
    is every four months.</p>

    <p>If an account or password is suspected to have been compromised, report 
    the incident to CSO and change all passwords.</p>

    <p>Password cracking or guessing may be performed on a periodic or 
    random basis by TechnoPark Corp. or its delegates.</p>

    <p>If a password is guessed or cracked during one of these scans, the 
    user will be required to change it.</p>

    <p>Any employee, vendors, contractors or users found to have violated 
    this policy may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including
    termination of employment.</p>

</text>

</article>


