<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<invisible/>

<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<label>Privacy Policy</label>
<intro>Learn about your privacy protection on our website</intro>
<next>about/legalnotes</next>

<keywords>
    privacy policy,
    BBB.org,
    TRUSTe,
    online privacy software development
</keywords>

<description>
    Privacy Policy, compliant with BBB and TRUSTe.
    TechnoPark Corp., referred to as "TPC", is committed to protecting your 
    privacy and ensuring you have a positive experience on our website(s). This 
    policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both 
    online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we 
    will treat it according to this policy.
</description>

<text>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp., referred to as "TPC", is committed to protecting your 
    privacy and ensuring you have a positive experience on our website(s). This 
    policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both 
    online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we 
    will treat it according to this policy.</p>

    <p>We encourage you to read this privacy policy to ensure you understand 
    TPC's privacy practices. This policy covers the TPC corporate website 
    (www.technoparkcorp.com) and is applicable worldwide.</p>

    <a href="http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.technoparkcorp.com&amp;sealid=101" 
        style="float: left; padding-right: 20px; border: none;" alt="TRUSTe.org"><png>//images/truste</png></a>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp is a licensee of the <ahref name="http://www.truste.org">TRUSTe</ahref> Web Privacy Seal Program.  
    <a href="http://www.truste.org">TRUSTe</a> is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to 
    build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use 
    of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the Web site 
    www.technoparkcorp.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment 
    to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and 
    have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by <a href="http://www.truste.org">TRUSTe</a>.</p>

    <a href="http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=10805219819" 
        style="float: left; padding-right: 20px; border: none;" alt="Click to verify BBB accreditation and to see a BBB report">
        <png>//images/bbb</png></a>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a proud holder of BBB Online Seal. The BBBOnLine trustmark confirms 
    a company is an accredited business in the BBB where they are based, has 
    met truth in advertising guidelines, discloses information about the business and its 
    policies, follows basic privacy and security practices, and responds appropriately 
    to problems that arise.</p>

    <p>If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact 
    Arthur Petrenko at 568 Ninth Street South 202, Naples, Florida, 34102, 
    <a href="${mailto:privacy}">${mailto:privacy}</a>.  If you do not 
    receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily 
    addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <a href="http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php">http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php</a>.
    TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.</p>

    
    <h1>Collection of PII</h1>

    <p>When TPC collects any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) on our corporate website, 
    we will express our need for the personal data at the point of collection.</p>

    <p>PII is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may 
    include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical 
    address, title, occupation, and other information required to provide a service, 
    deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested.</p>
    
    <p>Some of the reasons we collect your personal information include:</p>

    <ul>
        <li>Account registration and maitenance;</li>
        <li>Sales feedback;</li>
        <li>Online chat with sales representative;</li>
        <li>Newsletters;</li>
        <li>Online payments by credit card, and others.</li>
    </ul>

    
    <h1>Usage of PII</h1>

    <p>We will only use PII in the way we specified when it was collected. We will 
    not subsequently change the way PII is used without your consent. Some of 
    the ways we may use PII include:</p>

    <ul>
        <li>To provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content;</li>
        <li>To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information;</li>
        <li>To provide customer feedback and support;</li>
        <li>To invoice you, process credit card payments and communicate with our bank;</li>
        <li>To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products 
        and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary;</li>
        <li>To support recruitment inquiries;</li>
        <li>To understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites 
        to your preferences;</li>
        <li>To help diagnose problems with the server and to administer the website;</li>
        <li>To meet contract obligations.</li>
    </ul>    


    <h1>Updating of PII</h1>

    <p>We need your help in keeping the PII you have shared with us accurate and 
    up to date. Please notify us of any changes to your PII.</p>

    <p>Our sites DOES NOT allow you to make these updates yourself online. In order
    to update your PII you shall <a href="${mailto:privacy}">email us</a>
    or call at +1 (239) 243 0206.</p> 

    
    <h1>Unsubscribing</h1>

    <p>Subscriptions to our newsletters can be managed ONLY by direct request sent to us <a href="${mailto:privacy}">by email</a>.
    In addition, each email newsletter includes instructions on how you can un-subscribe from that particular mailing.</p>

    <p>You may also unsubscribe from TPC's newsletters by sending a letter, including your 
    name, email address and the title of the marketing material you wish to unsubscribe from to:</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp.<br/>
    Unsubscribe/Privacy<br/>
    568 Ninth Street South 202,<br/>
    Naples, Florida, 34102</p>


    <h1>Non-personal information collection</h1>

    <p>In some instances, TPC may collect non-personal (aggregate or demographic) 
    data through cookies, web logs, and web beacons. This information is used to 
    better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our website.</p>


    <h1>Sharing and Disclosure of PII</h1>

    <p>We do not sell or rent your PII to third-parties for marketing purposes unless you 
    have granted us permission to do so.</p>

    <p>We may share your PII within TPC or any of our worldwide subsidiaries for purposes of 
    data processing or storage.</p>

    <p>We may also share your PII with authorized third-party agents or 
    contractors in order to provide a requested service or transaction. For example, if we 
    need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. 
    We only provide third-party agents with the minimum amount of PII necessary to 
    complete the requested service or transaction.</p>

    <p>We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your 
    PII and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to 
    establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.</p>

    <p>We may collect and possibly share PII and any other additional information available 
    to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal 
    activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the 
    physical safety of any person, violations of TPC's terms of use, 
    or as otherwise required by law.</p>

    <p>While navigating TPC's web site you may be directed to content or functionality 
    that is hosted by a third party supplier, not on TechnoParkCorp.com. This is typically 
    done to host special events, such as contests. When information is collected on 
    behalf of TPC exclusively, TPC's privacy policy will be referenced on the site 
    and will govern how your information is used. For other, non-TPC sites, 
    the site owner's privacy policy will be referenced. It is TPC's practice to 
    require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with TPC's 
    privacy and security policies.</p>

    <p>We will ask you for your opt-in consent to share your PII with a third party for 
    any other reason.</p>
    

    <h1>Storage and Security of PII</h1>

    <p>TPC is committed to protecting the PII you share with us. We utilize a combination 
    of security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your 
    PII from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.</p>

    <p>When we transfer sensitive personal data (for example, credit card 
    information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) 
    encryption technology. To learn more about SSL, follow <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer">this link</a>.</p>

    <p>While we strive to protect your PII, we cannot ensure the security of the 
    information you transmit.</p>

    <p>We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your PII when you are on 
    the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of 
    letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.</p>

    <p>If you have any questions about security on our website, you can <a href="${mailto:privacy}">email us</a>.</p>


    <h1>Cookies</h1>

    <p>Cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes.
    TPC websites utilize cookies, although you can still access most of them even 
    if you choose to disable cookies in your browser. Some websites will not allow you 
    to complete certain activities if cookies are disabled.</p>

    <p>We do not link the information we store in cookies to any PII you submit while on the site.</p>

    <p>We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make 
    it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close 
    your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period 
    of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in 
    your Internet browser's help file. To learn more about cookies, follow the 
    <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie">link</a>.</p>

    <p>We store the identified of your latest login in cookie in order to avoid
    mutliple login requests when there are delays in site usage. We set a persistent 
    cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once.  
    Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of 
    our users to enhance the experience on our site.</p>

    <p>We use multiple third parties to monitor web traffic, statistics, advertisement 
    'click-through', and other activities on TPC's sites. Where authorized by TPC, 
    such third parties may use cookies, TPC's web log files, web beacons, and 
    other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous aggregate statistics on 
    TPC's website visitors.</p>

    <p>Current versions of web browsers offer enhanced user controls regarding 
    the placement and duration of both first and third party cookies. Search for 
    "cookies" under your web browser's Help menu for more information on cookie management 
    features available to you.</p>


    <h1>Linked websites</h1>

    <p>Our websites may provide links to other third-party websites which are outside 
    our control and not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy 
    policies posted on these (and all) sites.</p>

    <p>TPC uses live chat tool provided by <a href="http://www.liveperson.com">LivePerson.com</a>.
    You should be aware that information submitted by you in live chat may be read, collected
    or used by LivePerson.com, according to their privacy policies. For more information about
    LivePerson.com privacy policies follow <a href="http://liveperson.com/about/privacy.asp">the link</a>.</p>

    <p>TPC classifies your PII as confidential information. Confidential 
    information is protected by being stored on secure servers that only select TechnoPark 
    Corp. personnel have access to. The PII is encrypted to prevent 
    unauthorized access.</p>

    
    <h1>Changes to Privacy Policy</h1>

    <p>If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this 
    privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you 
    are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, 
    if any, we disclose it.</p>

    <p>We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review 
    it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, 
    by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.</p>

    <p>Your continued use of this site means you fully accept those changes. Last update of the Privacy Policy
    was made on <b>10/10/2008</b>.</p>

    
    <h1>Questions or Comments?</h1>

    <p>If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, 
    or your interaction with TPC by means of this site, please <a href="${url:contacts}">contact us</a> or
    send us <a href="${mailto:privacy}">an email</a>.</p>

</text>

<images>
    <truste>
MB5!.1PT*&amp;@H````-24A$4@```$0```!?&quot;`,```!FW)&#039;8````&quot;7!(67,```L3
M```+$P$`FIP8```*3VE#0U!0:&amp;]T;W-H;W`@24-#(&#039;!R;V9I;&amp;4``&#039;C:G5-G
M5%/I%CWWWO1&quot;2XB`E$MO4A4((%)&quot;BX`4D28J(0D02H@AH=D54&lt;$1144$&amp;\B@
MB`..CH&quot;,%5$L#(H*V`?D(:*.@Z.(BLK[X7NC:]:\]^;-_K77/N&gt;L\YVSSP?`
M&quot;`R62#-1-8`,J4(&gt;$&gt;&quot;#Q\3&amp;X&gt;0N0($*)&#039;``$`BS9&quot;%S_2,!`/A^/#PK(L`&#039;
MO@`!&gt;-,+&quot;`#`39O`,!R&#039;_P_J0IE&lt;`8&quot;$`&lt;!TD3A+&quot;(`4`$!ZCD*F`$!&amp;`8&quot;=
MF&quot;93`*`$`&amp;#+8V+C`%`M`&amp;`G?^;3`(&quot;=^)E[`0!;E&quot;$5`:&quot;1`&quot;`398A$`&amp;@[
M`*S/5HI%`%@P`!1F2\0Y`-@M`#!)5V9(`+&quot;W`,#.$`NR``@,`#!1B(4I``1[
M`&amp;#((R-X`(29`!1&amp;\E&lt;\\2NN$.&lt;J``!XF;(\N20Y18%;&quot;&quot;UQ!U=7+AXHSDD7
M*Q0V80)AFD`NPGF9&amp;3*!-`_@\\P``*&quot;1%1&#039;@@_/]&gt;,X.KL[.-HZV#E\MZK\&amp;
M_R)B8N/^Y&lt;^K&lt;$```.%T?M&#039;^+&quot;^S&amp;H`[!H!M_J(E[@1H7@N@=?&gt;+9K(/0+4`
MH.G:5_-P^&#039;X\/$6AD+G9V&gt;7DY-A*Q$);8&lt;I7??YGPE_`5_UL^7X\_/?UX+[B
M)($R78%&#039;!/C@PLST3*4&lt;SY()A&amp;+&lt;YH]&#039;_+&lt;+__P=TR+$26*Y6&quot;H4XU$2&lt;8Y$
MFHSS,J4BB4*2*&lt;4ETO]DXM\L^P,^WS4`L&amp;H^`7N1+:A=8P/V2R&lt;06&#039;3`XO&lt;`
M`/*[;\&#039;4*`@#@&amp;B#X&lt;]W_^\__4&gt;@)0&quot;`9DF2&lt;0``7D0D+E3*LS_&#039;&quot;```1*&quot;!
M*K!!&amp;_3!&amp;&quot;S`!AS!!=S!&quot;_Q@-H1&quot;),3&quot;0A!&quot;&quot;F2`&#039;&#039;)@*:R&quot;0BB&amp;S;`=*F`O
MU$`=-,!1:(:3&lt;`XNPE6X#CUP#_IA&quot;)[!*+R!&quot;01!R`@382&#039;:B`%BBE@CC@@7
MF87X(&lt;%(!!*+)&quot;#)B!11(DN1-4@Q4HI4(%5(&#039;?(]&lt;@(YAUQ&amp;NI$[R``R@OR&amp;
MO$&lt;QE(&amp;R43W4#+5#N:@W&amp;H1&amp;H@O09&#039;0QFH\6H)O0&lt;K0:/8PVH&gt;?0JV@/VH\^
M0\&lt;PP.@8!S/$;#`NQL-&quot;L3@L&quot;9-CR[$BK`RKQAJP5JP#NXGU8\^Q=P02@47`
M&quot;38$=T(@81Y!2%A,6$[82*@@&#039;&quot;0T$=H)-PD#A%&#039;&quot;)R*3J$NT)KH1^&lt;088C(Q
MAUA(+&quot;/6$H\3+Q![B$/$-R02B4,R)[F0`DFQI%32$M)&amp;TFY2(^DLJ9LT2!HC
MD\G:9&amp;NR!SF4+&quot;`KR(7DG&gt;3#Y#/D&amp;^0A\EL*G6)`&lt;:3X4^(H4LIJ2AGE$.4T
MY09EF#)!5:.:4MVHH501-8]:0JVAME*O48&gt;H$S1UFCG-@Q9)2Z6MHI73&amp;F@7
M:/=IK^ATNA&#039;=E1Y.E]!7TLOI1^B7Z`/T=PP-AA6#QXAG*!F;&amp;`&lt;89QEW&amp;*^8
M3*89TXL9QU0P-S&#039;KF.&gt;9#YEO55@JMBI\%9&#039;*&quot;I5*E2:5&amp;RHO5*FJIJK&gt;J@M5
M\U7+5(^I7E-]KD95,U/CJ0G4EJM5JIU0ZU,;4V&gt;I.ZB&#039;JF&gt;H;U0_I&#039;Y9_8D&amp;
M6&lt;-,PT]#I%&amp;@L5_CO,8@&quot;V,9LW@L(6L-JX9U@37$)K&#039;-V7QV*KN8_1V[BSVJ
MJ:$Y0S-*,U&gt;S4O.49C\&#039;XYAQ^)QT3@GG**&gt;7\WZ*WA3O*&gt;(I&amp;Z8T3+DQ95QK
MJI:7EEBK2*M1JT?KO3:N[:&gt;=IKU%NUG[@0Y!QTHG7&quot;=&#039;9X_.!9WG4]E3W:&lt;*
MIQ9-/3KUKBZJ:Z4;H;M$=[]NI^Z8GKY&gt;@)Y,;Z?&gt;&gt;;WG^AQ]+_U4_6WZI_5&#039;
M#%@&amp;LPPD!ML,SA@\Q35Q;SP=+\?;\5%#7&lt;-`0Z5AE6&amp;7X821N=$\H]5&amp;C48/
MC&amp;G&amp;7.,DXVW&amp;;&lt;:C)@8F(29+3&gt;I-[II23;FF*:8[3#M,Q\W,S:+-UIDUFSTQ
MUS+GF^&gt;;UYO?MV!:&gt;%HLMJBVN&amp;5)LN1:IEGNMKQNA5HY6:5855I=LT:MG:TE
MUKNMNZ&lt;1I[E.DTZKGM9GP[#QMLFVJ;&lt;9L.78!MNNMFVV?6%G8A=GM\6NP^Z3
MO9-]NGV-_3T&#039;#8?9#JL=6AU^&lt;[1R%#I6.MZ:SISN/WW%]);I+V=8SQ#/V#/C
MMA/+*&lt;1IG5.;TT=G%V&gt;Y&lt;X/SB(N)2X+++I&lt;^+IL;QMW(O&gt;1*=/5Q7&gt;%ZTO6=
MF[.;PNVHVZ_N-NYI[H?&lt;G\PTGRF&gt;63-ST,/(0^!1Y=$_&quot;Y^5,&amp;O?K&#039;Y/0T^!
M9[7G(R]C+Y%7K=&gt;PMZ5WJO=A[Q&lt;^]CYRG^,^XSPWWC+&gt;65_,-\&quot;WR+?+3\-O
MGE^%WT-_(_]D_WK_T0&quot;G@&quot;4!9P.)@4&amp;!6P+[^&#039;I\(;^./SK;9?:RV&gt;U!C*&quot;Y
M015!CX*M@N7!K2%HR.R0K2&#039;WYYC.D&lt;YI#H50?NC6T`=AYF&amp;+PWX,)X6&#039;A5&gt;&amp;
M/XYPB%@:T3&amp;7-7?1W$-SWT3Z1)9$WIMG,4\YKRU*-2H^JBYJ/-HWNC2Z/\8N
M9EG,U5B=6$EL2QPY+BJN-FYLOM_\[?.&#039;XIWB&quot;^-[%Y@OR%UP&gt;:&#039;.PO2%IQ:I
M+A(L.I9`3(A..)3P01`JJ!:,)?(3=R6.&quot;GG&quot;&#039;&lt;)G(B_1-M&amp;(V$-&lt;*AY.\D@J
M37J2[)&amp;\-7DDQ3.E+.6YA&quot;&gt;ID+Q,#4S=FSJ&gt;%IIV(&amp;TR/3J],8.2D9!Q0JHA
M39.V9^IGYF9VRZQEA;+^Q6Z+MR\&gt;E0?):[.0K`59+0JV0J;H5%HHURH&#039;LF=E
M5V:_S8G*.9:KGBO-[&lt;RSRMN0-YSOG__M$L(2X9*VI89+5RT=6.:]K&amp;HYLCQQ
M&gt;=L*XQ4%*X96!JP\N(JV*FW53ZOM5Y&gt;N?KTF&gt;DUK@5[!RH+!M0%KZPM5&quot;N6%
M?&gt;O&lt;U^U=3U@O6=^U8?J&amp;G1L^%8F*KA3;%Y&lt;5?]@HW&#039;CE&amp;X=ORK^9W)2TJ:O$
MN63/9M)FZ&gt;;&gt;+9Y;#I:JE^:7#FX-V=JT#=]6M.WU]D7;+Y?-*-N[@[9#N:._
M/+B\9:?)SLT[/U2D5/14^E0V[M+=M6&#039;7^&amp;[1[AM[O/8T[-7;6[SW_3[)OMM5
M`55-U6;59?M)^[/W/ZZ)JNGXEOMM7:U.;7&#039;MQP/2`_T&#039;(PZVU[G4U1W2/512
MC]8KZT&lt;.QQ^^_IWO=RT--@U5C9S&amp;XB-P1&#039;GDZ?&lt;)W_&lt;&gt;#3K:=HQ[K.$&#039;TQ]V
M&#039;6&lt;=+VI&quot;FO*:1IM3FOM;8ENZ3\P^T=;JWGK\1]L?#YPT/%EY2O-4R6G:Z8+3
MDV?RSXR=E9U]?B[YW&amp;#;HK9[YV/.WVH/;^^Z$&#039;3ATD7_B^&lt;[O#O.7/*X=/*R
MV^435[A7FJ\Z7VWJ=.H\_I/33\&gt;[G+N:KKE&lt;:[GN&gt;KVU&gt;V;WZ1N&gt;-\[=]+UY
M\1;_UM6&gt;.3W=O?-Z;_?%]_7?%MU^&lt;B?]SLN[V7&lt;G[JV\3[Q?]$#M0=E#W8?5
M/UO^W-COW&#039;]JP&#039;&gt;@\]&#039;&lt;1_&lt;&amp;A8//_I&#039;UCP]#!8^9C\N&amp;#8;KGC@^.3GB/W+]
MZ?RG0\]DSR:&gt;%_ZB_LNN%Q8O?OC5Z]?.T9C1H9?REY._;7RE_&gt;K`ZQFOV\;&quot;
MQAZ^R7@S,5[T5OOMP7?&lt;=QWOH]\/3^1\(&#039;\H_VCYL?53T*?[DQF3D_\$`YCS
M_&amp;,S+=L````@8TA230``&gt;B4``(&quot;#``#Y_P``@.D``&#039;4P``#J8```.I@``!=O
MDE_%1@```P!03%1%(1X&gt;(AX@(R(=)R@&gt;(R`@)&quot;`A)B,D)B&lt;@)R0E)R@@*24F
M*28H*2L@*R@I+&quot;DJ+BLL+BPM+3$B,&quot;TN,R\P,38B-3TD,S`Q-#$R-S0T.38W
M.C&lt;X.S@Y/#@Y/CP]-T$E.4,E/4DG/DLH0#T^0C]`0$\G0E$H150J1E@I2%LJ
M2UTK2EXL3%\J36,L4&amp;4M4VLM57`O6&#039;,N6G4P7&#039;HQ7GTQ0T)#1$)&quot;1T-$1T1%
M2$5&amp;2D=(2DA)3$E*3TQ-4$Y.4T]04E!15%%25E-45E156%9765=86EA97%I:
M7UQ=8%U&gt;85]@8V%B9&amp;)B9F-D9F1E:FAI;&amp;MK;FQM&lt;&amp;YN&lt;6]P&lt;G%R=&#039;)R=7-T
M=G5U&gt;&#039;9V&gt;&#039;=X&gt;GAY?&#039;I[?7M\?GQ]8H,R9XLS98HT:(PT:Y(U;Y@W;Y@X&lt;)HV
M&lt;YTX=:(W=:`X&gt;*4Y&gt;JDZ?*LZ@&#039;Y_@&#039;^`@;,\A;H]A[P]B;T_BL$^BL0]C,,^
MC,4]BL!`B\1`C,%&quot;C,1!CL5%D,9&amp;D&lt;9)D\=-DLA)D\A,E,A.ELE1F,M3F&lt;I5
MFLI8F\Q9G,M:G,Q9G&lt;Q=GLU@H&lt;YAHLYDHM!FIM!KJ-%NJM-SKM5ZL=9]L=A]
M@8&quot;`A(*&quot;A8.$AH2%B(&gt;&#039;B(&gt;(BHB)C(F*CHV-D(Z/D(^0DI&quot;1E)*3EI25F):7
MFIB9G)J:G9N&lt;GIV=H)Z?H)^@HJ&quot;AI*.CI:2DJ*:GJ*&gt;HJ:BHK*NKKJRML*^O
ML:^PL;&quot;PMK6UN+:VN[JZO+N[O;R]M-&gt;#L]B&quot;M-B#M=F$M]F(N-J*N=J-N]R/
MO-N/N]R0O-N0O=R1OMV5P+^_P+_`P-V5P]^=Q&gt;&quot;?QN&quot;@R.*DS.6JT&gt;:SU&gt;FZ
MV.J^P&lt;&#039;!QL7&amp;R,?&#039;R&lt;C(S,O+S&lt;W-T=&#039;1U-/4U=75V=G9WMW&gt;VNK!V^S#V^S%
MW.S&quot;W.S&amp;WNW)X-_?X&gt;[,X^_0Y?#3Y_&#039;8Z/+9ZO+&lt;Z?3;Z_3&gt;X&gt;&#039;AY./DY&gt;7E
MZ.?HZ&gt;GI[&gt;WM[?7B[_;D\.[O\._P\/;E\?;H]/CM\?&#039;Q]?7U]OGQ^/?X^OSU
M^/CX^OSX_/WY_O[^````Q&#039;N5#```&quot;4Q)1$%4&gt;-K,F&amp;MP5=45QW]KGW-OW@DA
MY.:2\%#D(0\+`@(*&amp;(D5,1%(`$5\C+4B4%%&#039;G7&#039;LC/W2]EO]AN,+12&amp;*4@A4
MH&quot;K0,2T4JJVU&quot;0F!X%0&amp;&gt;&gt;9%0@+D&lt;7//VOUP\R!`&quot;&quot;&amp;TTWT^W&#039;O.V?=_UW^M
MO?]K[25*WX&gt;Y`1BX4/=D^\V\I?,M0,R2N0Z&#039;7^&amp;WXX$_?$A^/ZI?/E(UY)&#039;&lt;
MU`V?M$]^?50GBNI1:1_WJQOYXDZOU6*1`E75MT2J]5!_1(38+8L[)A=KQW`A
M?I:QY97ANWW,`X(3\?Y1M^_YC[H8_&#039;*M;V&#039;6YD)W;&#039;:-V$(&quot;MUG\T!**ES9+
M5%7?=J5*5=657%4]DR:#NEJ2)K-5]=!V555/)$]5]&gt;#L:`FN;E753L=*Y_\F
MWT9C5]?%V;WKJAF5$YGH`!R:]J=FIW+9XFZB8TO_QKBNCWXIC&lt;\$I[Y7&gt;]&amp;C
MY&gt;&gt;&quot;!ZH&gt;DRT&#039;+Z93&#039;:$3&#039;0CT%Y%M6BRRL8..]UZ2())4HJHJ;IYJI&lt;C:^OKJ
M1/?MB^FTC7!U;1V!30]BP`-0$.3IBL]7#&gt;3&quot;\HYYIRU+4U(&quot;Y]@![J54IJYH
M7.F-R8-$V+@8*&quot;`V&quot;&gt;_(B#DL?V!/4:NO;:(/LD8`W&#039;,Y&#039;7)5%POK5&#039;6P^-;7
MGWE7W`=4ER2NJ=&#039;:Z6Y*!YV6_G)?J^J66E6]S&quot;&gt;YJHV#)+9&lt;=8L@KBM$&#039;]!#
M?L3MYT=6=H#HQ\+@&gt;=-D&lt;F,&#039;R%M&quot;IR6ZUY49K:J?)B%(^A&gt;J&gt;F&quot;V*XB;VZ2J
M*N2IJJZ)0XA;IZH2V&lt;7&#039;ZNU8!RBUT2.!@YX=&amp;0W-?ZDWHT9&#039;O%#S36/4F!$`
ME$C42(&quot;Z/&gt;&lt;39B8#HC=F%P-8K%S/)9T@5:5?MUZ7&quot;;X[Q@?;Z/RPMNDZM4F-
M[Z$)8*!A;8NY;EUL+:@&quot;`R4M?7%J&lt;QD8^*9O(OTM&amp;`CU+;ZM8+JHT?4,YP:E
MC)Y`]$:`&amp;*.J/8&amp;Y5UE(ZETH&quot;H547-^$N)BKV=HMB`G5_?68M8+C6=E/&lt;L;T
M&gt;.FE)=JZ^W#(BA7&#039;`P&amp;I.ULV^-Y4O780-&gt;;/!YO$&quot;F(]PH@5*]CC&#039;]Z4&#039;7NY
MLILK@YB6[3\Z`M8,3KK=^#6\O[&#039;RK!7&#039;.[KFX0&#039;7:LGYW]=)6&amp;SJD.FN4:-&amp;
MLY3S&gt;W]H$4(?CYGM7)-CS^4WNQ[]Y@[`@&amp;F[$N&gt;T?G40QRL+9SN7T;F,HEY8
MWVP]&gt;^L3`1&lt;4Q:`&amp;U$3-&gt;3HY#-_O4NV13GC3!&lt;&gt;3VV&lt;)ZIK`S$&quot;*R]E3#7L:
MP&quot;0]OJ&#039;&amp;]&lt;JBLGH&quot;T9UG;-A=DJ:&quot;&gt;]^D1``&quot;`6:4[*I1XUORV3&amp;A&gt;$J,T]4G
ME]*I.XS(N%1K2%DY*Z&amp;3^(27%_HQ[OP!%MW&lt;@T]DNSC&lt;&lt;J\1D_Y2!@)H*&amp;0!
MW*G/^#&#039;^A4;&lt;ZIJKTZFHD7#,`V#2GG.!IK+=9SUBIXP&lt;*G#S4Q^TF+AQ!SW^
MN-1&gt;!&lt;3LP`F/\@GQ*URPWVUM`6C8M2O]T2`,6_`)YIXCS=[9ZH!V+P4-U7C.
MW4;MHS$0?F-#2WN4*]X\&quot;C)QD,$=X5GVVN[UQ&#039;X-W.IB,H99*#PFBL8D)[D8
MFMX_&quot;?(P,$.$(RW=TY$ZU^-.P&gt;0B_*O0X&quot;3?/\ZE_M&quot;VD`GEOVI(3SMIHH8&gt;
M1&lt;^E=!OB\`FLB1=BAT+X&quot;U6&quot;+TUP(6GJ\F@X4P22&quot;22#?-=]B)L5&amp;&gt;3&quot;-($?
M&amp;S#QR_T1&quot;X?F@11:&amp;.[&quot;)(MMZMZQ+8*-!&gt;T/&#039;+&gt;0W2&amp;*X^.Q9YH@(0:B&lt;&gt;1L
MEY*D&quot;XA:3WR15$*18#(Z77&gt;G,5H-$@.Q)NR$&#039;=.=%$2/$SL)3`*1\O/XJ8Y7
M!\*&amp;?]=`&quot;.Q8K`F;[J*3,-N@H.&lt;!1XUNC&amp;B24:.N@2^-&amp;C7H_5U2R&amp;5[)_)`
M/.`GTJE(!J.TWU[!#5=*7E(&#039;I-@^IM%O+(Q+O-9JJ1N0^I/@YJA&gt;JQE7!)$M
M8&quot;&lt;.,GJ-F?W*&quot;;WB!&quot;+/!B^&quot;&lt;&#039;/]VDN0T&quot;&lt;A\+^0Z[9;D?*+&amp;4]%:Z]\@JEY
M1\&amp;=_F)VDC&#039;6G_&#039;(*X.YY:FH[LSHKBHX]M6]QDH@D-D&lt;DGAC!6RTK[67]8G9
M6;HT$9&quot;8F,@ATQ9M&quot;?&gt;^R*EX?&gt;X$G[27_J&lt;VGD9-;T$,307;,P&lt;,BS&gt;$JD_O
MKD2-Z;TE&amp;%IV81S7T_#5JCN]*DC;`;ZU&gt;QI77;&amp;];8_\EXKAR`K4R&amp;Y1-/)I
M.F[TDFUT!9\8C9T_VG_A\-;02XWO&amp;(P^&amp;ES=2&#039;#A0*H*3F8\7+;3+$[__O,&gt;
M+-&amp;H9R&gt;VGO#?D&gt;8$X@4P_08:,EX84E65\?.HL0-C[*))I[_L,&lt;3S@D6;6F-F
M&#039;/&gt;UZ;D1ZRYU5AUS@AH&quot;\B85%6B/&gt;R?#?A&amp;6YET7:TG_N!]/.%JA!FY*KR@(
M6^F!CHFCN4V3.]*\0YUM&gt;Y+AI:6J]!0=K9%417TH*I$#AIRS(V/`^%&quot;.OZ&#039;/
M)/0&lt;XNVZ(COXT&amp;MIV,1!0X&lt;.`CA?&#039;+,L/7W%,K]P[.3?8Y^TEVJE&quot;UUSPZG=
M,V=EV7,6C7U&gt;[+G?8(7/DFY^T5*,!?/9P)L7%EQ:Z2FO5W&lt;EE&#039;17]#^K0SK8
M`-ZIH%L1AN!D_:Z2Q,3S9S4AV9Z\&gt;#&gt;EO(HHNS_OTYJ?DX6!&quot;?Z^=&quot;Y\8\!`
MTL*H/F`L2FOKGYS&gt;5&#039;=])VQGP*+TCB:,C73#&gt;@\B6+E!G9S_R0G]FCO#A0(P
M&gt;K2WXY2YXS8!:O;&lt;,A[J&quot;H=&#039;EP%V^/C]/V&quot;=L2.H+1PSYOL2`\38YIFI&gt;%N9
M[X#J`1%$Y-W*J0@RIU%5Z^-2FE3?DX_R$1&#039;)UAP1P?&gt;Q%LM*78^(R#U;^:FG
MZU@2Z?@U[-LW3;;O*Y\N2PZ6S)*&#039;5%47R3;UAL76YLN:TM+2&lt;LV1K&lt;6;$Q):
M]O.&lt;KN?-XN+B,F^.;*U.&#039;-C0T3;,DD8MYCY5;0SXZU6UE`=U/PLT7]:5EY&gt;W
M:HY4J9&lt;IM&lt;6LTO7R:5-3DZ&gt;5&quot;1D/RC;M`O(I&#039;ZBJ9KMEJJI3_6&lt;64Z+Y@HB4
M:XZLSG_&lt;-UF+996NQ^?S^4I4UPESVQO=;2-6=OX,J/,&amp;`#S_Q+8=4\9AR9T/
M`0O+Q$Y;VS9U9BI$P6._.OX^G8WN+&amp;G4,XEQ1:KK98:JJM8FQ/&amp;1:KYL5575
M&#039;&quot;G:[,YHU8A/-K:UVC.E2;5+HSOY@]&quot;4NX8_GK@:@&#039;ZS+\3E`&quot;P;/G3X`BP9
M&gt;7E[UU[6$K\X900S!19\^UIYRN3?#8F\^/7)Q_I!4B9`/#F-#N_7;UC@NWLJ
F&quot;7?&#039;MOUX8*9I5[;_DV7_GP$`HJR`BB!@)@4`````245.1*Y&quot;8((`
`
    </truste>

    <bbb>
MB5!.1PT*&amp;@H````-24A$4@```#P```!@&quot;`,```!V;N&#039;,````&quot;7!(67,```L3
M```+$P$`FIP8```*3VE#0U!0:&amp;]T;W-H;W`@24-#(&#039;!R;V9I;&amp;4``&#039;C:G5-G
M5%/I%CWWWO1&quot;2XB`E$MO4A4((%)&quot;BX`4D28J(0D02H@AH=D54&lt;$1144$&amp;\B@
MB`..CH&quot;,%5$L#(H*V`?D(:*.@Z.(BLK[X7NC:]:\]^;-_K77/N&gt;L\YVSSP?`
M&quot;`R62#-1-8`,J4(&gt;$&gt;&quot;#Q\3&amp;X&gt;0N0($*)&#039;``$`BS9&quot;%S_2,!`/A^/#PK(L`&#039;
MO@`!&gt;-,+&quot;`#`39O`,!R&#039;_P_J0IE&lt;`8&quot;$`&lt;!TD3A+&quot;(`4`$!ZCD*F`$!&amp;`8&quot;=
MF&quot;93`*`$`&amp;#+8V+C`%`M`&amp;`G?^;3`(&quot;=^)E[`0!;E&quot;$5`:&quot;1`&quot;`398A$`&amp;@[
M`*S/5HI%`%@P`!1F2\0Y`-@M`#!)5V9(`+&quot;W`,#.$`NR``@,`#!1B(4I``1[
M`&amp;#((R-X`(29`!1&amp;\E&lt;\\2NN$.&lt;J``!XF;(\N20Y18%;&quot;&quot;UQ!U=7+AXHSDD7
M*Q0V80)AFD`NPGF9&amp;3*!-`_@\\P``*&quot;1%1&#039;@@_/]&gt;,X.KL[.-HZV#E\MZK\&amp;
M_R)B8N/^Y&lt;^K&lt;$```.%T?M&#039;^+&quot;^S&amp;H`[!H!M_J(E[@1H7@N@=?&gt;+9K(/0+4`
MH.G:5_-P^&#039;X\/$6AD+G9V&gt;7DY-A*Q$);8&lt;I7??YGPE_`5_UL^7X\_/?UX+[B
M)($R78%&#039;!/C@PLST3*4&lt;SY()A&amp;+&lt;YH]&#039;_+&lt;+__P=TR+$26*Y6&quot;H4XU$2&lt;8Y$
MFHSS,J4BB4*2*&lt;4ETO]DXM\L^P,^WS4`L&amp;H^`7N1+:A=8P/V2R&lt;06&#039;3`XO&lt;`
M`/*[;\&#039;4*`@#@&amp;B#X&lt;]W_^\__4&gt;@)0&quot;`9DF2&lt;0``7D0D+E3*LS_&#039;&quot;```1*&quot;!
M*K!!&amp;_3!&amp;&quot;S`!AS!!=S!&quot;_Q@-H1&quot;),3&quot;0A!&quot;&quot;F2`&#039;&#039;)@*:R&quot;0BB&amp;S;`=*F`O
MU$`=-,!1:(:3&lt;`XNPE6X#CUP#_IA&quot;)[!*+R!&quot;01!R`@382&#039;:B`%BBE@CC@@7
MF87X(&lt;%(!!*+)&quot;#)B!11(DN1-4@Q4HI4(%5(&#039;?(]&lt;@(YAUQ&amp;NI$[R``R@OR&amp;
MO$&lt;QE(&amp;R43W4#+5#N:@W&amp;H1&amp;H@O09&#039;0QFH\6H)O0&lt;K0:/8PVH&gt;?0JV@/VH\^
M0\&lt;PP.@8!S/$;#`NQL-&quot;L3@L&quot;9-CR[$BK`RKQAJP5JP#NXGU8\^Q=P02@47`
M&quot;38$=T(@81Y!2%A,6$[82*@@&#039;&quot;0T$=H)-PD#A%&#039;&quot;)R*3J$NT)KH1^&lt;088C(Q
MAUA(+&quot;/6$H\3+Q![B$/$-R02B4,R)[F0`DFQI%32$M)&amp;TFY2(^DLJ9LT2!HC
MD\G:9&amp;NR!SF4+&quot;`KR(7DG&gt;3#Y#/D&amp;^0A\EL*G6)`&lt;:3X4^(H4LIJ2AGE$.4T
MY09EF#)!5:.:4MVHH501-8]:0JVAME*O48&gt;H$S1UFCG-@Q9)2Z6MHI73&amp;F@7
M:/=IK^ATNA&#039;=E1Y.E]!7TLOI1^B7Z`/T=PP-AA6#QXAG*!F;&amp;`&lt;89QEW&amp;*^8
M3*89TXL9QU0P-S&#039;KF.&gt;9#YEO55@JMBI\%9&#039;*&quot;I5*E2:5&amp;RHO5*FJIJK&gt;J@M5
M\U7+5(^I7E-]KD95,U/CJ0G4EJM5JIU0ZU,;4V&gt;I.ZB&#039;JF&gt;H;U0_I&#039;Y9_8D&amp;
M6&lt;-,PT]#I%&amp;@L5_CO,8@&quot;V,9LW@L(6L-JX9U@37$)K&#039;-V7QV*KN8_1V[BSVJ
MJ:$Y0S-*,U&gt;S4O.49C\&#039;XYAQ^)QT3@GG**&gt;7\WZ*WA3O*&gt;(I&amp;Z8T3+DQ95QK
MJI:7EEBK2*M1JT?KO3:N[:&gt;=IKU%NUG[@0Y!QTHG7&quot;=&#039;9X_.!9WG4]E3W:&lt;*
MIQ9-/3KUKBZJ:Z4;H;M$=[]NI^Z8GKY&gt;@)Y,;Z?&gt;&gt;;WG^AQ]+_U4_6WZI_5&#039;
M#%@&amp;LPPD!ML,SA@\Q35Q;SP=+\?;\5%#7&lt;-`0Z5AE6&amp;7X821N=$\H]5&amp;C48/
MC&amp;G&amp;7.,DXVW&amp;;&lt;:C)@8F(29+3&gt;I-[II23;FF*:8[3#M,Q\W,S:+-UIDUFSTQ
MUS+GF^&gt;;UYO?MV!:&gt;%HLMJBVN&amp;5)LN1:IEGNMKQNA5HY6:5855I=LT:MG:TE
MUKNMNZ&lt;1I[E.DTZKGM9GP[#QMLFVJ;&lt;9L.78!MNNMFVV?6%G8A=GM\6NP^Z3
MO9-]NGV-_3T&#039;#8?9#JL=6AU^&lt;[1R%#I6.MZ:SISN/WW%]);I+V=8SQ#/V#/C
MMA/+*&lt;1IG5.;TT=G%V&gt;Y&lt;X/SB(N)2X+++I&lt;^+IL;QMW(O&gt;1*=/5Q7&gt;%ZTO6=
MF[.;PNVHVZ_N-NYI[H?&lt;G\PTGRF&gt;63-ST,/(0^!1Y=$_&quot;Y^5,&amp;O?K&#039;Y/0T^!
M9[7G(R]C+Y%7K=&gt;PMZ5WJO=A[Q&lt;^]CYRG^,^XSPWWC+&gt;65_,-\&quot;WR+?+3\-O
MGE^%WT-_(_]D_WK_T0&quot;G@&quot;4!9P.)@4&amp;!6P+[^&#039;I\(;^./SK;9?:RV&gt;U!C*&quot;Y
M015!CX*M@N7!K2%HR.R0K2&#039;WYYC.D&lt;YI#H50?NC6T`=AYF&amp;+PWX,)X6&#039;A5&gt;&amp;
M/XYPB%@:T3&amp;7-7?1W$-SWT3Z1)9$WIMG,4\YKRU*-2H^JBYJ/-HWNC2Z/\8N
M9EG,U5B=6$EL2QPY+BJN-FYLOM_\[?.&#039;XIWB&quot;^-[%Y@OR%UP&gt;:&#039;.PO2%IQ:I
M+A(L.I9`3(A..)3P01`JJ!:,)?(3=R6.&quot;GG&quot;&#039;&lt;)G(B_1-M&amp;(V$-&lt;*AY.\D@J
M37J2[)&amp;\-7DDQ3.E+.6YA&quot;&gt;ID+Q,#4S=FSJ&gt;%IIV(&amp;TR/3J],8.2D9!Q0JHA
M39.V9^IGYF9VRZQEA;+^Q6Z+MR\&gt;E0?):[.0K`59+0JV0J;H5%HHURH&#039;LF=E
M5V:_S8G*.9:KGBO-[&lt;RSRMN0-YSOG__M$L(2X9*VI89+5RT=6.:]K&amp;HYLCQQ
M&gt;=L*XQ4%*X96!JP\N(JV*FW53ZOM5Y&gt;N?KTF&gt;DUK@5[!RH+!M0%KZPM5&quot;N6%
M?&gt;O&lt;U^U=3U@O6=^U8?J&amp;G1L^%8F*KA3;%Y&lt;5?]@HW&#039;CE&amp;X=ORK^9W)2TJ:O$
MN63/9M)FZ&gt;;&gt;+9Y;#I:JE^:7#FX-V=JT#=]6M.WU]D7;+Y?-*-N[@[9#N:._
M/+B\9:?)SLT[/U2D5/14^E0V[M+=M6&#039;7^&amp;[1[AM[O/8T[-7;6[SW_3[)OMM5
M`55-U6;59?M)^[/W/ZZ)JNGXEOMM7:U.;7&#039;MQP/2`_T&#039;(PZVU[G4U1W2/512
MC]8KZT&lt;.QQ^^_IWO=RT--@U5C9S&amp;XB-P1&#039;GDZ?&lt;)W_&lt;&gt;#3K:=HQ[K.$&#039;TQ]V
M&#039;6&lt;=+VI&quot;FO*:1IM3FOM;8ENZ3\P^T=;JWGK\1]L?#YPT/%EY2O-4R6G:Z8+3
MDV?RSXR=E9U]?B[YW&amp;#;HK9[YV/.WVH/;^^Z$&#039;3ATD7_B^&lt;[O#O.7/*X=/*R
MV^435[A7FJ\Z7VWJ=.H\_I/33\&gt;[G+N:KKE&lt;:[GN&gt;KVU&gt;V;WZ1N&gt;-\[=]+UY
M\1;_UM6&gt;.3W=O?-Z;_?%]_7?%MU^&lt;B?]SLN[V7&lt;G[JV\3[Q?]$#M0=E#W8?5
M/UO^W-COW&#039;]JP&#039;&gt;@\]&#039;&lt;1_&lt;&amp;A8//_I&#039;UCP]#!8^9C\N&amp;#8;KGC@^.3GB/W+]
MZ?RG0\]DSR:&gt;%_ZB_LNN%Q8O?OC5Z]?.T9C1H9?REY._;7RE_&gt;K`ZQFOV\;&quot;
MQAZ^R7@S,5[T5OOMP7?&lt;=QWOH]\/3^1\(&#039;\H_VCYL?53T*?[DQF3D_\$`YCS
M_&amp;,S+=L````@8TA230``&gt;B4``(&quot;#``#Y_P``@.D``&#039;4P``#J8```.I@``!=O
MDE_%1@```P!03%1%____`&amp;65?[+*O]CD/XNOP-GE[_7X0(RP#VZ;+X&amp;H7YZ\
MW^OQS^+K&#039;WBBC[O0G\77;ZC#3Y6VK\[=\/;YT./K@++*H,;88)^]0(NOX.SR
M&lt;*G$4)6V____````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````
M````````````````````7!43E0```!UT4DY3________________________
M_____________P!9AN=J```$NDE$051XVJQ8RY:C.`R]LHV-@0(JF][T_W_;
MS)DY594*A)=MS2(O2(`BZ?&#039;.#R%9NKJ2H=\`6M+_XJE1!B4!!325=?\\)XN_
MI2D[J]#LXR\\/?PQ:JV`R*OE,^GRUG[H!&gt;3&#039;\@&#039;M\^7-\*&#039;:%5F$0:[9+O9K
MFW[UWD&amp;L;&amp;8,1*N:5RY,`/:)?DDXK0&quot;@,=GRD6A)O*#+6/*XD))YWNAP]5:O
MU*SG2&quot;U9Y$;?]$KZI^X\P587REG5D0^S5@]W&quot;[&amp;H&#039;Q0O:7XPL_6[9T)U-[K/
MW5;A&gt;&amp;;MJ#&lt;*US/0Z-16L^=B$[8*T]RUY4;AFGXFEF5O!_NX5FT.U?%1=[91
M6!&lt;(Z;W+[T&quot;VF%74ID,/X\9K9HI96A+.6\###\4X9F%ZE!;,S@Z`3`&#039;LY0UK
M9AM(-%U3H6Z*R^K0;Z*A\DQ`I08`&amp;9\FCWDQ)ZRO]&amp;4S`,B)B![#/I_/MW.M
MRP%\9X`1&amp;]E3T&amp;@D`!*B`MC,)+?1Y`!0[K&lt;2X!27/2&quot;S&gt;C-[^FR:B$7%_7;J
MG98W;MZK9\I-,7;9DE^6&#039;+87V3JIK*:D[ZZ`,O[I$MM_OIDSWEXHL4!FB6BY
M%*Z#I/)V`98;-`,@6FF&#039;?H!GBF*U(5K7G*TV0X_NR)IQ5LBU$O0H/%_L3]_]
MB?33=MG.&#039;PEPK=GL-CILDAD+0%D,53.9)&lt;]ANX]_JO1KB3&#039;F@WD2F@O5A71&#039;
MG^77$(:-&quot;+LB2_:3D/G38^-2#ZK9]O&#039;6V&lt;JX&amp;G./=3WD%789?:^&amp;RD^;L&quot;F^
MJX-XBGK;::EA_=A6&quot;#ZY56J/%B&quot;`&amp;-#&amp;`3T+!D0`4NENWI\!GB?`7+.C[R?$
M6XMUD!1^O*H3`+&gt;RGIDQ%:N&#039;&quot;O&lt;-F),V)F`8`&#039;MZ]`4Z]5(WL^:+^[#BOKA:
M]_:7F!#]]R2IVK&quot;;%V9F3@GH$@`@9F81`TUV&quot;@=SE!M@&gt;,2V(CH[]HU(X5H=
M)1$)21&lt;&amp;+Z_&#039;9A%V1W-OTT:I6TQ)!2&quot;J`6@&#039;(&amp;T`V/VER.H!@&amp;A&#039;[IY+#,#(
M2:\NG0R3@%+Q,4_Z`#*&gt;6&amp;ZGK:_VNCG&gt;F9T&gt;+I?TAW$[4&#039;8U$#&gt;W5KI-O&gt;&#039;V
MCYGD==&amp;GGH/_M[`ZL&lt;!+&gt;OF/-$MYUOO&gt;`:7L=U&quot;FW\$Z*CEQ1&quot;80910%$^@\
MD8%*.`!TO;/]&quot;&quot;;[U*(?/,H]:G#5US&amp;S\DA;,WC%,7CPS*Z-N?=FHCGD/-B6
MW2&quot;&amp;T+`C0`1BI@[4I=\B#/#,(@B2WG,8P&quot;/-L=_WEN`01]&quot;(@5A%&amp;M&amp;)654Z
M2G@%(#N3RUE8I^J][C*7-B2/HK%HDMIB(+*PR0&gt;/^C*&quot;3+^*=FQV&#039;WQ;JCZK
M9,^)LTT&lt;FK)7/1#@DNB8.B`.G#I`!#^&lt;W@P$BOQ\!97JK@.)507C_&amp;*&lt;!3.7
M)$&quot;&lt;1:ZU)&quot;03!!$S4]X&lt;&lt;AE&lt;%$^KY$VS@&amp;X$*%!0+D&#039;HB1P4,R@`7(A#&quot;&quot;K;
M+R+,-^=_&#039;&quot;H[.@L`4EC`,R/??Z8F=4,\A[#SFU9Z6/&#039;F21.W(`I&amp;U00!@J7D
M.X)RP[B\1.+V?I,`&lt;JN!\ET#[T(JD#WE?)$&quot;4IP9^GRZ5&#039;FC#J._2?X`H^P&gt;
M4/8K&lt;PS?6H4&amp;&quot;$&gt;+%K$;Q2&quot;.Z?=?QG&lt;OI93)!(@&#039;\X)L+#JA\*L&#039;O57/RKZY
B82&lt;5H`?6S].(*S7^&amp;P!JE,!PIP.XN0````!)14Y$KD)@@@``
`
    </bbb>
</images>

</article>


