<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>8/29/2009</date>

<invisible/>
<label>PDD</label>
<title>
    Puzzle Driven Development (PDD) to help in distributed projects
</title>     

<keywords>
    puzzle driven development,
    distributed programming,
    remote team,
    quality control,
    continuous integration
</keywords>

<description>
    One of the biggest problems in parallel distributed
    programming has been solved with a patent-pending method
    called Puzzle Driven Development (PDD).
</description>

<text>

    <p>Read more on this topic
        in <a href="http://www.phparch.com/magazine/2010/august/">php|Architect, August 2010</a> 
        article "<b>Prevent Conflicts in Distributed Agile PHP Projects</b>", by Yegor Bugayenko.</p>

    <p>Parallel programming in a distributed team is a tricky
    and risky process, especially if your project wants to be successful and
    delivered on time. Subversion helps isolate programmers in
    their branches, but when they start to reintegrate into trunk,
    conflicts may effectively ruin hours or days of work.</p>

    <p>Distributed development of software over the last decade has been
    growing in popularity. This is mostly due to the continuous improvement
    of the quality of communication channels and the emergence of new methods
    of interaction between us, in the Internet. Nowadays, brick-and-mortar offices become
    less effective when a software project requires the participation of
    engineers with different skills, experience, and price.</p>

    <p>One of the biggest problems in parallel programming is conflicts
        of source code. People tend to make chaotic changes and then later
        fail to merge their results with similar contributions made by
        others. Puzzle Driven Development (PDD) solves the problems, by means
        of using so called "puzzles" inside source code.</p>
        
    <p>More on this topic to be revealed later, when patent application
        is published by USPTO.</p>

</text>
</article>
