<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>5/22/09</date>

<invisible/>
<title>
    PROFES 2009 Attendees Glimpse Method behind Superior Cost Estimating Accuracy
</title>     

<keywords>
    software cost estimating,
    cost estimating,
    cost estimation,
    project cost estimating,
    software project size estimating,
    scope champions,
</keywords>

<description>
    Software development project managers now have a better way to 
    estimate the cost of development, thanks to TechoPark Corp. Its 
    CEO will, for the first time, showcase the method used in its 
    revolutionary approach to cost estimating for software projects, at 
    a conference dedicated to process improvement of software development.
</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL (PRWEB) May 22, 2009 - On June 16, 2009, Yegor Bougaenko, 
    CEO of TechnoPark Corp., will present a paper on a "Method for Software Cost 
    Estimating Using Scope Champions" at <a href="http://www.profes2009.org">PROFES 2009</a>, the 10th International Conference 
    on Product Focused Software Development and Process Improvement, 
    in Oulu, Finland from June 15-17, 2009.</p>

    <p>This paper highlights the proprietary method behind TechnoPark Corp.'s software 
    that uses a new revolutionary approach to software project cost estimating. 
    Rather than estimating the entire project scope, Arthur Petrenko, 
    TechnoPark's Marketing Director, explains that the "method estimates a 
    very limited number of selective elements called Scope Champions, rather that trying 
    to estimate the entire project. Then a formula is applied to calculate the total 
    cost. Clients find this method saves time and improves accuracy of the estimate."</p>

    <p>While TechnoPark applied for the method's patent last fall, Bougaenko decided 
    to wait for the conference to unveil the process in order "to take advantage of 
    PROFES' industry reach, as the number and breadth of companies there showcases 
    companies' need for and commitment to the process improvement of software development, 
    a sphere in which TechnoPark and its innovations excel," mentions Petrenko.</p>

    <p>Non-attendees who wish to examine Bougaenko's paper will be able to do 
    so when TechnoPark publishes the article along with presentation slides on TechnoPark's 
    website immediately following the conference. Conference materials will also be published 
    by Springer in the Lecture Notes of Computer Science (LNCS) Series.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a specialized project management firm providing quality 
    development services to companies worldwide. TechnoPark effectively manages extreme 
    requirements, tight deadlines, and limited budgets, setting the new 
    standard in providing solutions to customers that are proven to be both high 
    value and high quality. For more information about how TechnoPark is 
    revolutionizing development, visit <a href="${url:innovations/scope-champions}">www.TechnoParkCorp.com</a>.</p>

    <p>
        <a href="http://www.prweb.com/releases/2009/05/prweb2448764.htm">prweb.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.prlog.org/10243020-profes-2009-attendees-glimpse-method-behind-superior-cost-estimating-accuracy.html">prlog.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.free-press-release.com/news/200905/1243236227.html">free-press-release.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.1888pressrelease.com/profes-2009-attendees-glimpse-method-behind-superior-cost-es-pr-121766.html">1888pressrelease.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.pr.com/press-release/154407">pr.com</a>
    </p>

</text>
</article>
