<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>6/23/09</date>

<invisible/>
<title>
    TOOLS EUROPE 2009 Attendees to Discover How Work Can Be a Game in Risk Identification
</title>     

<keywords>
    risk game,
    risk identification,
    risk identification distributed,
    risk management,
    risk planning
</keywords>

<description>
    Software project managers now have a new tool in their arsenal when it 
    comes to risk identification - a game. Developed by TechnoPark Corp., this 
    innovative new method will be unveiled at the TOOLS 2009-hosted SEAFOOD '09 
    conference. Already field tested, this method has been shown to save considerable 
    time and costs and improve the quality of risk identification.
</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL, June 23, 2009 - On July 3, 2009, attendees at 
    the <a href="http://tools.ethz.ch/">TOOLS EUROPE 2009</a>-hosted event 
    <a href="http://seafood.ethz.ch/2009/">SEAFOOD '09</a> (the Third International 
    Conference on Software Engineering Approaches for Offshore and Outsourced 
    Development), which will be held at ETH Zurich, Switzerland on July 2-3, 2009, 
    will learn how TechnoPark Corp.'s CEO, Yegor Bougaenko, has developed and 
    identified a game as a superior choice for certain risk identification 
    scenarios for software projects.</p>

    <p>The method detailed in the paper Bougaenko will present had its 
    genesis last summer in a large, risky project for one German customer. 
    Since none of the methods to identify project risks were suitable for the 
    online-chat environment needed by its distributed team, TechnoPark developed 
    its own method. The paper is especially relevant to this year's 
    SEAFOOD theme, "Enabling Global Partnerships to Deliver on Business Needs," 
    as it is specifically tailored to instances where, among other factors, the 
    project team is multi-lingual and distributed. However, in line with TechnoPark's 
    efforts to "create value for all companies, the method is appropriate 
    even for mono-lingual teams in a concentrated location," mentions Bougaenko. </p>
 
    <p>"Since project management is a difficult discipline, while risk management is 
    especially so, TechnoPark aims to simplify complex things, ensuring 
    success in our customers' projects through professional project management. This 
    method is an excellent example of our latest research in this direction," says 
    Arthur Petrenko, TechnoPark's Marketing Director. "In fact, this method resulted 
    in a savings of over 200 man-hours and more than 9% of budget on the 
    very first project we deployed it on," adds Petrenko. </p>

    <p>Interested parties can obtain the conference materials from TechnoPark Corp., who will 
    make them available for download on its website right after the end of 
    the conference. Conference materials will also be published 
    by <a href="http://www.springer.com/">Springer Verlag</a>.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a specialized project management firm providing quality development 
    services to companies worldwide. TechnoPark effectively manages extreme requirements, 
    tight deadlines, and limited budgets, setting the new standard in providing 
    solutions to customers that are proven to be both high value and high quality.</p>

    <p>
            <a href="http://www.pr.com/press-release/160837">pr.com</a> |
            <a href="http://openpr.com/news/85245.html">openpr.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.pr-inside.com/tools-europe-2009-attendees-to-discover-how-work-can-be-a-game-in-risk-identification-r1339445.htm">pr-inside.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.1888pressrelease.com/tools-europe-2009-attendees-to-discover-how-work-can-be-a-ga-pr-128699.html">1888pressrelease.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.free-press-release.com/news/200906/1245744882.html">free-press-release.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.sanepr.com/TOOLS-EUROPE-2009-Attendees-to-Discover-How-Work-Can-Be-a-Game-in-Risk-Identification_87085.cfm">sanepr.com</a> |
        <a href="http://www.i-newswire.com/pr299213.html">i-newswire.com</a>
    </p>

</text>
</article>
