<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>12/23/08</date>

<title>
    TechnoPark Reveals Quality of Process for Software Development
</title>     

<keywords>
    patent, quality of process, metrics, software metrics
</keywords>

<description>
    Patent Pending for TechnoPark: Method for Measuring Quality of Process
</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL, December 18, 2008: TechnoPark Corporation (TPC) 
    announces they have filed for a patent with the United States Patent and 
    Trademark Office (USPTO).  To ensure the quality of their process, TPC 
    created an original procedure that includes a quality requirements definition, 
    quality metrics collection, numeric calculations and methods for team motivation.</p>

    <p>By calculating requirement weights, TPC has created software called "thePanel" which 
    allows software developers to accurately predict the quality of their process.  
    Once the necessary calculations are made, they are delivered to project 
    managers, senior managers and project stakeholders.</p>

    <p>Says Arthur Petrenko, TechnoPark Corp.'s Marketing Director, "This method and 
    automated process is at the core of our business.  It gives us an advantage 
    and allows us to be unique in the quality we provide to our customers.  
    Our invention makes us the only company in the market offering an automated quality 
    of process calculation through the entire software project.</p>

    <p>By delivering a dependable prediction of the quality of process, all parties 
    involved in a project understand the end goal and how everyone will work 
    together to achieve that end goal.  The approach works for individual projects and 
    for businesses trying to maintain multiple processes. The method for measuring 
    quality of process has already helped TPC save 10-40% on their costs and 
    increased team motivation in 10 projects during 2008.</p>

    <p>The application to the USPTO was filed on November 4th 2008 and has a pending 
    number of 12/264,370. This method is going to be patented by the European 
    Patent Office (EPO) next year.  Submitting the Quality of Process patent to the US 
    Patent and Trademark Office follows a series of steps over the past year that 
    TPC has taken to fortify their reputation with their clients and to secure their 
    intellectual property.  These steps include pending patents and achieving ISO 9001:2000 certification.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a US-based outsourcing software development company with development centers 
    across the globe, including the Ukraine, India and China.</p>

</text>
</article>