<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>10/9/08</date>

<title>
    Estimates Are More Reliable with TechnoPark Corp., new patent-pending invention
</title>     

<keywords>
    patent, estimation, patent-pending, software size, software cost,
    cost estimation, estimate
</keywords>

<description>
    TechnoPark Corp. Registers a New Invention with USPTO.
</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, Florida October 7, 2008 - TechnoPark Corp. has registered 
    an estimating method for software project completion with the 
    United States Patent Trademark Office (<a href="http://www.uspto.gov">USPTO</a>).  
    This invention greatly reduces the time it takes to provide an estimate to 
    a client.  The estimates are more accurate, which in turn helps clients 
    plan for the on-deadline completion of a project.</p>

    <p>Using uniquely developed formulas, TechnoPark uses a limited number of 
    examples in a client's code to calculate the time it will take a 
    programmer to build a project.  By using the most complex examples of code, 
    TechnoPark Corp.'s invention defines the amount of effort needed to 
    complete a software product.</p>

    <p>The technical explanation of the new invention deals with sets of 
    requirements.  Based on a limited set, up to seven, the requirements, 
    existing on the same level of abstraction, are estimated with an existing 
    estimation approach.  The requirements, called scope champions, are chosen for 
    their complexity and then calculated for the time it takes to complete them. </p>

    <p>Until TechnoPark Corp. pioneered these formulas, programmers often had 
    to expend a great deal of time to provide a reasonably accurate estimate.  
    This was detrimental to client and vendor alike.  Vendors don't want 
    to waste hours estimating when they could be working billable hours.  Clients 
    are more satisfied when their projects are done on time and under budget.  
    TechnoPark Corp.'s invention gives it an edge when estimates are made 
    because customers know they can count on a well researched, proven 
    estimating technique.</p>

    <p>Arthur Petrenko, TechnoPark Corp.'s Marketing Director, says, 
    "We have been working on new inventions like the estimation formula to benefit 
    our clients.  In the future, we are going to continue to develop and 
    patent our ideas and methods.  This is all part of our larger 
    dedication to excellence and reliable business practices."</p>

    <p>USPTO issued an application number for TechnoPark, 
    <b>US12/193,010</b>, and they are excited to announce the invention.</p>

</text>
</article>