<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>4/8/08</date>

<title>A new platform for the Premium SMS market has reached its second release</title>     

<keywords>
    premium sms software, rich media, mobile market, adobe flex,
    custom software development, mobile platform, PSMS, mobile marketing,
    mobile content
</keywords>

<description>The Premium SMS market in the US is growing, with forecasted 
turnover in 2009 of $1,9 bln. TechnoPark Corp., a Floridian custom software development company, 
is launching a second release of the Premium SMS marketing platform.</description>

<text>

    <p>Premium SMS (also called reverse billed SMS or Mobile Terminated Billing) is a 
    payment method, which allows the Customer to pay with his mobile phone bill, 
    but without usage of a Credit card. In order to pay for some service, the 
    Customer sends SMS to the Provider's number and receives a digital access code 
    to his phone. At this moment, the Customer's phone bill is charged and the 
    money is transferred to the Provider's account. This payment style is 
    ideal for so-called "micro-payments".</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is developing a premium SMS management platform for Dialect 
    Properties LLC., a Texas-based company, since 2006. The product is branded 
    by MsgWire.com label on the US market.</p>

    <p>"This project challenged our team, since it had a number of serious and 
    unforeseen risks caused by connectivity with third-parties and the necessity to 
    perform functional testing remotely" - says Arthur Petrenko, Marketing Director 
    of TechnoPark Corp.</p>

    <p>The mobile market has tremendously grown just in a few years. 
    Premium SMS billing is also constantly rising and now has a significant share 
    of the whole mobile market in the USA. The first ever Premium SMS Report, 
    that was presented by Telephia, have shown that Premium SMS sales in Q1 2007 were 
    about $273 million. Most of this revenue was as payment for mobile content and 
    voting/sweepstakes entries.</p>

    <p>The reason for such PSMS popularity lies in the fact that it is a very 
    successful way to reach the Customer. The field of premium messaging became the 
    field for marketing experiments due to extremely high coverage. As an example, 
    NBC's 'Deal or No Deal' became a real premium SMS hit and generated nearly 
    half of the volume and revenue of voting/sweepstakes entries in the first 
    quarter of 2007.</p>

    <p>"The new version of the system is making our plans of licensing very possible 
    now. We will be able to deliver flexible, stable and powerful products. 
    We already have a number of requests from future license-holders, who will buy 
    the platform this summer with an annual flat fee" - says Vonn Butler, 
    CEO of Dialect Properties LLC.</p>

    <p>The newest version of MsgWire.com was released this March. The system 
    is integrated with MX Telecom and OpenMarket XML gateways, thus reaching 
    more than 98% of US mobile phone users.</p>

    <p>MX Telecom is a leading international company in the field of wireless 
    services. It has been a Mobile Marketing Association (MMA) Consumer Best 
    Practices Committee member from 2005 and was two times named in the top twenty 
    of the Deloitte Technology Fast 50 and led this rank in 2006. It was 
    also featured several times in the Sunday Times "Tech Track 100", 
    which lists the fastest growing UK technology businesses due to growth of 
    more than 100 percent a year.  Employing only 50+ workers, it provides 
    various IT solutions to more than 500 corporate clients in the UK, 
    Ireland, Australia, the USA and Canada.</p>

    <p>OpenMarket, which was founded in 1994, offers OpenMarket SMPP API, 
    HTTP/XML API and SMS SDK for development of e-commerce mobile applications. 
    Among OpenMarket global customers are Lycos.com, AOL.com, and the Wall 
    Street Journal Interactive Edition; major industrials such as Acer, Ingram 
    Micro, Milacron, and Siemens; and 10 of the world's top 13 national 
    telephone companies. Its content management software is used by companies 
    including Lucent Technologies, Financial Times of London, Hitachi, and 
    Chase Manhattan Bank. Headquarted in Burlington, Massachusetts, and it 
    has international offices in Australia, Canada, France, Germany, Italy, 
    Japan and The Netherlands.</p>

    <p>MsgWire.com allows mobile marketing campaigns creation in a number of clicks. 
    The manager defines a list of recepients (mobile numbers and names of users), 
    and a chain of messages and dependencies between them. The system automatically tracks 
    user behavior, sends/receives SMS and runs the campaign. The manager gets status 
    reports in different formats.</p>

    <p>The system is constructed with Adobe Flex - the most powerful Rich Internet 
    Applications development platform from Adobe Systems Incorporated.</p>

    <p>Adobe Flex is a number of technologies, developed by Fortune 500's 
    "most admired" company, and is in active use by multiple Fortune 500 companies. 
    It is made for designing and deployment of cross platform and rich Internet applications 
    based on the proprietary Adobe Flash platform. Released in 2004, it keeps 
    all media functionality that is offered by Flash but has much more capability. 
    It successfully works for such famous sites like the Sony Ericsson Product 
    Catalogue, Yahoo! Messenger for the Web, Pikeo online photo sharing 
    and Picnik online photo editing.</p>

</text>
</article>