<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<title>Risk identification and response planning</title>
<label>Risk List</label>
<intro>Read about our Risk management tool - Risk List</intro>
<next>process/risk/strategy</next>

<description>
	Risk List is a document with a list of current risks, together with
	mitigation plans, risk strategies and risk analysis data (probability and impact)
</description>

<keywords>
	risk list,
	risk identification,
	risk,
	risk cause,
	risk response plan,
	risk strategy,
	risk mitigation plan
</keywords>

<term>risklist</term>

<text>

	<p>A Risk List is created by the project manager during the <a href="${url:process/time/inception}">Inception Phase</a>
	and presented to you prior to a <a href="${url:process/time/lco}">LCO Milestone</a>.</p>
	
	<p>The project team participate in the process of identifying possible Risks, and assist the project manager
	in answering the question, 'what could go wrong?'.
	A Risk List may include hundreds of Risks, but a maximum of 20 are presented
	to you for <a href="${url:process/risk/strategy}">Risk Strategies</a> selection and 
	Risk response plans approval.</p>
	
	<p>You are responsible for choosing which Risk Strategy you wish to 
	implement for each Risk. The following is an example of a Risk List:</p>

		<table>
		<tr>
			<th>Risk ID and Description</th>
			<th>Mitigation Plan</th>
			<th>Contingency Plan</th>
		</tr>

		<tr>
		<td>RISK1, Data provider changes the API on its own schedule, without prior 
		notification. The next change may happen before the project 
		release Milestone, and the system won't work.</td>
		<td>Develop a configurable XML-based integration module that will 
		allow dynamic API changes without code re-factoring (240 staff-hours)</td>
		<td>Integration module re-factoring  (180+ staff-hours, 10+ days)</td>
		</tr>

		<tr>
		<td>RISK2, Video compressing module is open-source software and doesn't have any guarantees or support.
		Defects may be revealed in the module.</td>
		<td>Perform module testing (70 staff-hours) and re-identify Risks</td>
		<td>Defect removal in the module (220+ staff-hours)</td>
		</tr>
	</table>	

	<p>The Mitigation plan is what actions will be taken in advance to remove Risk responsibility from
	you. The Contingency Plan is what shall be done when the Risk occurs.</p>
	
	<p>When a Risk List is presented, you select a Risk Strategy for
	each item listed.
	You can choose to accept the Risk, or select to implement the Mitigation Plan. For example:</p>

	<table>
		<tr>
			<th>Risk ID</th>
			<th>Rank</th>
			<th>Strategy</th>
		</tr>

		<tr>
		<td>RISK1</td>
		<td>Mitigate</td>
		<td>Extend budget for 240 staff-hours and develop a configurable 
		XML-based integration module that will 
		allow dynamic API changes without code-refactoring</td></tr>

		<tr>
		<td>RISK2</td>
		<td>Accept</td>
		<td>Do nothing, but if defects are revealed, the budget will be extended for 
		220 staff-hours in order to remove the defect.  If this does not help, the budget will be extended
		for 500+ staff-hours for the development of a custom video compressing module</td></tr>
	</table>	

	<p>If you accept the Risk, it means that you agree to take full responsibility for it.  
	If the Risk happens, the Contingency Plan will be implemented, resulting in an extension of the project 
	<a href="${url:process/time/schedule}">Schedule</a>, <a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a>,
	and <a href="${url:process/cost/budget}">Budget</a>. 
	In the example above, the customer has chosen to accept RISK2.  As a result, the customer may have to pay
	for an additional 220 hours in the event that the Risk takes place, as detailed in the Contingency Plan.
	</p>

	<p>If you choose to implement the Mitigation Plan, this means that the project team will attempt to prevent the 
	Risk from happening at all, and try to neutralize the Risk consequences. In any
	case, you will not be held responsible for the impact to the project if the Risk should occur. 
	In the example above, if the customer chose to use the Mitigation Plan for RISK1, the project team would add a XML-based integration
	module to the Scope.  If the Risk happened to occur in spite of this measure, the team would then have to implement 
	the Contingency Plan, however, the customer would not be responsible for additional staff hours.</p>
	
	<p>As shown in the examples above, each Risk has the probability to impact the <a href="${url:process/cost}">Cost</a>, 
	<a href="${url:process/scope}">Scope</a> and <a href="${url:process/time}">Schedule</a>. 
	Qualitative and quantitative Risk analysis is done by the project manager in order to select
	the top 20 Risks.</p>
	
	<p>As shown in the diagram, Risk management is an iterative process:</p>

	<p align="center"><tikz>
\begin{tikzpicture}
	[node distance = 2.5cm, 
	auto, thick]

	\node [block, text width=2.7cm] (identified) {New Risks Identified};
	\node [block, below of=identified] (developed) {Risk Plans Developed};
	\node [block, below of=developed] (strategies) {Risk Strategies Selected};
	\node [block, text width=5cm, below of=strategies] (changes) {Changes to Scope, Cost and Specification};

	\path [line] (identified) -- (developed);
	\path [line] (developed) -- (strategies);
	\path [line] (strategies) -- (changes);
	\path [line, fill=none] (changes.east) -| (4,2) -| (identified.north);
\end{tikzpicture}
	</tikz></p>
	
	<p>New Risks can possibly be revealed during the whole lifecycle of the project until the final Release Milestone
	is reached. A Risk List is only provided to you during the Inception Phase. You are
	not responsible for any Risks identified after the LCO Milestone, as long as subsequent Risks are not
	related to new Specifications.</p>
	
	<p>The Risk List is a very important document in any software development project and
	is used by all project team members. The Risk List is not a part of the project
	<a href="${url:process/warranty/deliverables}">Deliverables</a>, but you still can access it for review.</p>
	

</text>

<concepts>
	<c5 name="process/risk/risk">Risk is an atomic element of Risk List</c5>
	<c3 name="process/cost/budget">Budget includes Risk responses and Risk reserves</c3>
	<c5 name="process/time/schedule">Schedule also includes Risk responses and Risk reserves</c5>
</concepts>

</article>


