<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<title>Cause, risk, effect</title>
<label>Risk</label>
<intro>Learn what a Risk is in software development projects, and how it is defined</intro>
<next>process/risk/risklist</next>

<description>
    A Risk in software development project is an event that may have an impact 
    on the outcome of the project. Risk differs from problems or issues because a risk refers
    to the future potential of loss/benefit. Problems or issues, however, are conditions or states
    of affairs that exist in a project at present time.
</description>

<keywords>
    risk,
    software development risk,
    cause-risk-effect,
    risk identification,
    "cause risk effect" format,
    risk source,
    risk effect,
    risk cause
</keywords>

<term>risk</term>

<text>

    <p>A Risk in software development project is an event that may have an impact 
    on the outcome of the project. Risk differs from problems or issues because a risk refers
    to the future potential of loss/benefit. Problems or issues, however, are conditions or states
    of affairs that exist in a project at present time.</p>

    <p>Risks should be identified for the following reasons:</p>

    <ul>
        <li><a href="${url:process/time/schedule}">Schedule</a> can be developed more realistically based on accurate Risk planning</li>
        <li><a href="${url:process/cost/budget}">Budget</a> is more accurate when it includes reservations for possible Risks</li>
        <li><a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a> is unambiguous when Risks are revealed in advance</li>
        <li>Outcomes are more predictable if the project team is prepared to handle unexpected negative interruptions</li>
    </ul>

    <p>Risks are found and identified by the project team, project manager and you during the 
    whole project lifecycle. Risk management is an iterative process. The sooner a Risk
    is identified, the faster it can be managed and mitigated.</p>

    <p>Major Risk identification
    activities are performed during the <a href="${url:process/time/inception}">Inception Phase</a>. 
    <a href="${url:process/risk/strategy}">Risk Strategies</a> 
    and Risk response plans are baselined on a
    <a href="${url:process/time/lco}">LCO Milestone</a> in the <a href="${url:process/risk/risklist}">Risk List</a>.</p>

    <p>Risks are typically <i>sourced</i> by people, Requirements, software, hardware, and communications.
    Mid-size software projects include hundreds of Risks.  Not all Risks are identified and managed,
    only those that appear to be the most severe.</p>

    <p>Each Risk is defined in a 'Cause-Risk-Effect' format. The cause may be the 
    source of the Risk, the Risk is what may or may not happen, and the effect is the impact to the project
    objectives, should the Risk actually happen.</p>

    <p>Examples of Risks from typical software development projects include:</p>

    <table>
        <tr>
            <th>#</th>
            <th>Cause</th>
            <th>Risk</th>
            <th>Effect</th>
        </tr>
        <tr><td>RISK1</td>
        <td>Deployment server will be purchased by the customer on 8/26</td>
        <td>System installation and configuration may take more than 3 days</td>
        <td>Project will be delayed</td></tr>

        <tr><td>RISK2</td>
        <td>Data provider changes API on its own schedule, without prior notification</td>
        <td>Next change may happen before the end of project release Milestone</td>
        <td>Integration module re-factoring will take and 40+ additional staff-hours</td></tr>

        <tr><td>RISK3</td>
        <td>System analyst doesn't have experience in medical business software</td>
        <td>System analyst and the customer may have difficulty communicating and understanding </td>
        <td>Inception Phase will take more than 3 weeks, the customer may become frustrated, and the project may be canceled</td></tr>
    </table>    

    <p>When Risks are identified and discussed with the project team, the project
    is prepared to handle any negative interruptions. 
    This decreases the probability of a Risk taking place throughout the course of the project.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c3 name="process/risk/risklist">Risk List is a register of all Risks in the software development project</c3>
    <c5 name="process/risk/strategy">Risk response plans are planned for all major risks</c5>
    <c7 name="process/cost/budget">Budget calculation is based on Risk analysis</c7>
</concepts>

</article>


