<?xml version="1.0"?>

<!--
    Version tracking section:

    9/15/07 Yegor - first version
    10/2/2007 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->

<article>

<title>Pay by credit card</title>
<label></label>
<intro></intro>
<next></next>

<text>

    <p>I authorize TechnoPark Corp. (568 Ninth Street South 202, Naples, Florida 34102,
    tel. (239) 243 0206) to charge the amount of my invoice to this credit
    card. The transaction will appear in the credit card statement as 'TECHNOPARK CORP'. The
    card will be charge by Fifth Third Bank, Florida, USA.</p>

    <p>The CVV2 number is the 3-digit code that appears on the back of Visa and
    MasterCard cards. On American Express cards, the CVV2 is the 4-digit number
    that appears on the front of the card above the last 4 digits of the card number.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. provides a 100% refund in the case that it does
    not comply with the terms and conditions of delivery and acceptance stated in Software
    Development Contract. Deliverables are delivered according to
    SRS, in electronic form, by email.</p>

    <img name="../../about/truste_seal_ctv.gif"
        ahref="http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.technoparkcorp.com&amp;sealid=101"
        style="float: left; padding-right: 20px;" >TRUSTe</img>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp is a licensee of the <ahref name="http://www.truste.org">TRUSTe</ahref> Web Privacy Seal Program.
    [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org) is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to
    build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use
    of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the Web site
    www.technoparkcorp.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment
    to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and
    have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org).</p>

    <img name="../../about/bbbseal1.gif"
        ahref="http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=10805219819"
        style="float: left; padding-right: 20px;" >Click to verify BBB accreditation and to see a BBB report.</img>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a proud holder of BBB Online Seal. The BBBOnLine trustmark confirms
    a company is an accredited business in the BBB where they are based, has
    met truth in advertising guidelines, discloses information about the business and its
    policies, follows basic privacy and security practices, and responds appropriately
    to problems that arise.</p>

</text>

</article>
