<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code accidentally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
-->

<article>

<categories>

    <category>Testing</category>
    <category>Quality Management</category>
    <category>Quality Control</category>

</categories>

<title>Quantitative quality control</title>
<label></label>
<intro></intro>
<next></next>
<invisible/>

<description>
    
    The main feature of this project was an online data-storage with 
    a files version control for the metal company with more than 20 offices 
    and 600 employees. The technical solution here was to use PHP+SVN tools. Since 
    SVN is open source software and this connection might be risky, 
    we decided to increase the amount of the component testing. Thus, 
    we planned to find and fix 100 defects of this feature instead of 
    estimated 50. And really, when 50 defects were found the PHP+SVN connection 
    was not stable still. Only when more than 80 defects were fixed, was 
    the System stable. 20 defects left were related to appearance only, 
    and finally we accepted the project with the appropriate quality rating.

</description>

<tex>

    The objectives of this Project were to develop the company's 
    corporate system with file storage, data analysis and visualization, 
    news RSS import, email feedback and a 3rd party PHPBB forum. 
    The project cost was 1302 s/h, the schedule -- 5 months. 

    We chose an SVN system to store the company's data and PHP to 
    implement the connection to this storage. Lessons learned from 
    previous projects contained information about issues of open source 
    SVN software. It was decided to plan on more testing of this 
    feature. So we planned to find and fix double the amount 
    of defects instead of the usual estimated number. 

\begin{tikzpicture}
    \node [storage] (php) at (2,5) {PHP5 engine};
    \node [storage] (svn) at (8,5) {SVN storage};
    \path [line, triangle 60-triangle 60] (svn) -- node[above, text width=2cm, text centered] {connection protocol} (php);

    \draw [-angle 60, draw=tpcBlue, ultra thick] (php.north west) 
        .. controls +(-3,+2) and +(-3,-2) .. node [left] {unit testing} (php.south west); 

    \draw [-angle 60, draw=tpcBlue, ultra thick] (php.north) 
        .. controls +(+12,+3) and +(+12,-3) .. node [pos=0.8, below] {auto testing} (php.south); 
\end{tikzpicture}

    This plan was correct and when the 100th bug was fixed, the 
    system gained an acceptable quality level. Quantitative quality control 
    is a powerful tool to manage a project's quality.

</tex>

</article>

