<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
	Version tracking section:

	10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>12/13/06</date>

<title>VoIPX: In VoIP Traffic Exchange Software Talks</title>

<description>TechnoPark Corp. finished development of new VoIP Traffic
 Exchange Platform. The exchange is available at voipx.com.</description>

<text>
<p>The introduction of new VoIP exchange platform is a desired event.
 Demand for high-quality IP Telephony Exchanges is stimulated by the fast
  growth of the industry.</p>

<p>According to the figures posted on<ahref
  name="http://www.voipmonitor.net/2006/12/08/VoIP+Grows+To+82+Million+Subscriptions.aspx">
  VoipMonitor.net</ahref>, subscribers to VoIP services grew 18 percent to 8.2
  million users in the third quarter of 2006. VoIP revenues are up two and a
  half times to $732 million across the U.S., compared to last year at
  $298 million. Predictions have the market growth projected at 1.5
  million new subscriptions in the fourth quarter to round out the year
  with 9.7 million or nearly 8.7 percent of all U.S. households.</p>

<p>LearningGuide Solutions studied the user's intentions about VoIP. The poll,
 conducted between June and October 2006, found that 30% were already using
 IP telephones, 34% intended to in the next twelve months and 16% were
 considering it. </p>

<p>"This is in an increase on previous expectations of the growth of VoIP,
 signalling further change in the workplace," said Cees Louwers, Managing
 Director, LearningGuide Solutions. "Users will be faced with changes in
 how to use the most fundamental piece of office equipment, as telephones
 become part of the office network."</p>

<p>Voice over Internet Protocol is developing in aggressive competitive
 environment. Its customers and profits are growing fast, however the
 competition with POTS (Plain Old Telephone Systems) is still severe.
 Having a number of advantages like cheap or even free connection, IP
 Telephony often falls behind the POTS in quality and security of
 connection. The problem is within eyeshot of VoIP exchange software
 developers, and efforts targeted to its solution are made.</p>

<p>VoIPX.com developed by Technopark Corp. is a new generation platform
 heedful of the latest demands of IP Telephony. The system is user-oriented
 thus it is aimed at fulfilling of a number of basic features: user-friendly
 interface, comprehensive billing, quality of calls, and security.</p>

<p>The platform is developed with the use of modern programming technologies
 enabling its high scalability. The technologies include Ajax, used for
 interface design, and powerful PostgreSQL database. </p>

<p>Dynamical routing provides system's switching to better-quality channel
 automatically. In so doing the system is able to select a channel with the
 same capabilities and price. Dynamical routing may improve connection
 quality without increasing cost of a call. </p>

<p>Modularity of system's architecture enables making software components
 updates in order to maintain the proper level of security.</p>

<p>The software enables processing the requests for origination/termination
 of connections through H.323 and SIP protocols. With VoIPX.com, user can
 control origination and termination session process, get detailed statistics
 reports for each session, supervise service quality, be advised on the
 choice of appropriate equipment, etc.  The Exchange Platform has an
 easy-to-use and comprehensive integrated billing system. </p>

<p>VoIPX Platform has already been tested and released by outsourcing
 software development company TechnoPark Corp., and is available at
  <ahref name="http://www.voipx.com">http://www.voipx.com</ahref>.</p>

</text>
</article>