<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>09/04/06</date>

<title>New Generation Software for VoIP</title>

<description>TechnoPark Corp. starts development of multifunctional platform 
for traffic trading.</description>

<text class="html">

<ul><small>
September 4, 2006 <ahref name="http://www.prleap.com/pr/46635/">PR Leap</ahref>
 - New Generation Software for VoIP: TechnoPark Corp. Starts Development of 
 Multifunctional Platform for Traffic Trading
</small></ul>

<p>IP-telephony market faces the grand problem connected with provision of 
well organized traffic trading process. New generation VoIP exchange software 
is expected to solve the problem.</p>

<p><b>VoIP market trends</b>
<br />IP telephony is a relatively new kind of telecommunication activity. It 
emerged in the 90's and succeeded in competing with traditional kinds 
of voice-to-voice communication. Still, the intermediaries supress the 
market's development with their high tariffs and limited capabilities. That 
leads to an increase in service costs for the final customers and decreases the number 
of available routes. As a result, profits of both sellers (terminators) and 
buyers (originators) fall.</p>

<p>According to industry experts, IP telephony market tends to eliminate 
intermediaries which may lead to price-cutting for customers. </p>

<p><b>VoIP Exchanges vs Clearing houses</b>
<br />Until recently, clearing houses have been the most popular intermediaries 
in VoIP traffic trading. However, even though they assume the lion's share of 
trading job and spare the exchange participants most routine troubles, 
clearing houses have a number of grave disadvantages and run the gauntlet. 
Having bought traffic from a terminator, they are able to sell it for a much 
higher price. Opponents of clearing houses argue that they are 
an effective money-making scheme generating a questionable value.</p>

<p>IP Telephony Exchange is a new model of traffic exchange. It is already 
employed in the U.S. and western Europe, but is not widely used yet. De facto 
VoIP Exchange is an online marketplace for traffic trading with a clear market 
pricing basis. The model is targeted to providing more freedom to terminators 
and originators, therefore it is gaining popularity worldwide. </p>

<p><b>New Generation Software</b>
<br />This gradation from intermediary to close cooperation proves that IP 
telephony market success is becoming dependent on VoIP exchange software 
developers. VoIP exchange software must meet a number of requirements 
including every aspect of operation, such as high-quality connection, 
failure free compliance of equipment of any manufacturer, online statistics, 
etc. The automation of the process is another vital issue. Despite the claimed 
automation, the majority of online marketplaces are managed manually now.</p>

<p>New generation VoIP exchange software is expected to solve the numerous 
problems of IP telephony market participants. Technopark Corp.'s new product 
is an innovative solution. The VoIP platform development project has been 
launched in August 2006. </p>
<p>Dynamical routing will be the main innovation. Dynamical routing is an 
ability to switch to a better quality channel automatically. In so doing the 
system is planned to select a channel with the same capabilities and price. 
Dynamical routing may improve connection quality without increasing cost of a 
call. No VoIP exchange has provided such opportunity until now.</p>

<p>The project is also aimed to enable processing the requests for origination or
termination of connections through H.323 and SIP protocols and provide a 
number of new useful functions as well as those already implemented by other 
exchanges. The software will enable overall control over the origination and 
termination session processes, access to detailed statistics reports for each 
session, supervision over service quality, advising operators on the choice of 
appropriate equipment, etc.  The TechnoPark Corp.'s VoIP Exchange Platform is 
also planned to have integrated billing system. </p>

<p>Final testing and product release are scheduled for October 2006. The 
product will be introduced to the U.S. market. </p>

</text>
</article>