<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
	Version tracking section:

	10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>11/16/06</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp.'s Product Certified by VISA</title>

<description>The first Ukrainian company was found to be compliant against 
PCI Data Security Standards. In October, software developed by the Ukrainian 
outsourcing company TechnoPark Corp. was certified by VISA.</description>

<text>

<p>The importance of the introduction of this list of requirements is obvious 
because of the ever-growing number of thefts and illegal accesses to 
confidential data of cardholders. In fact, PCI DSS is a list of requirements 
for handling and keeping personal information of payment system clients. 
Without a doubt, the standard can never fight off the problem back and edge, 
but the results prove that it really works: according to statistics, no PCI 
DSS compliant system has been compromised yet. </p>

<p>Unfortunately, only 20% of all payment systems in the world have been 
certified now. Among them, there is only one mobile payment processor; 
with its certification, MPPS has become the second PCI DSS compliant mobile 
payment system in the world. </p>

<p>MPPS is mobile payment processing system enabling its users to pay for goods
 and services using only their mobile phones. Like other mobile payment systems,
 MPPS needs to gather and store its customers' information which includes 
 personal and confidential data. It makes such systems to focus on protection 
 and security of the gathered information. Data security is even more 
 important task in the light of vigorous growth of this young but very 
 prospective industry. High profits make mobile payment industry an attractive
 target for fraudulent attacks. </p>

<p>The PCI Data Security Standards are not an obligatory condition of payment 
systems operation. Nevertheless, VISA strongly encourages all online payment 
service providers to go through the certification. PCI DSS requirements cover 
mostly the piece of software, which operates the system, as this is the crucial
factor providing the service's reliability. Thus, the software developer is 
responsible for PCI DSS compliance.</p> 

<p>Software for MPPS was developed by the Ukrainian TechnoPark Corp. The company, 
together with MPPS Solutions Ltd.'s Management, passed through the certification
procedures.</p> 

<p>MPPS applied for the certification in August 2006. In September, the first 
stage of the certification was held - a so called Onsite Audit. Onsite Audit is 
the audit held in the company's office. MPPS software as well as documentation 
were checked and examined by representatives of the British One Sec Ltd. which 
is the official VISA's auditor. The process took several days. The first stage of the
examination provided a list of comments and needed improvements which had to 
be implemented during one month. </p>  

<p>The second stage - Last Clean Scan - was the final examination resulting in 
overall decision. It was held in October, and the certificate for MPPS was 
issued on October, 31. Now the company can guarantee high reliability and 
security of its services to both clients and partners.</p> 

<p>PCI Data Security Standards have been used for more than 5 years, however 
there are very few PCI DSS compliant eastern European software companies 
focused on online payments. Despite many of them are able to offer high-quality 
products, most IT companies are frustrated by the great efforts, both 
intellectual and financial, needed to complete the certification. The good news is 
that some outsourcing software development companies have already realized that 
the game was worth the candle. With the availability of reliable developers, 
risk of outsourcing online-payment projects to the Ukraine decreases. </p>

<p>The Ukrainian software product's PCI DSS compliance is an important 
achievement for the whole Ukrainian IT outsourcing industry. TechnoPark Corp. 
has made the first step towards changing the image of Ukrainian IT products 
from "cheap staff" to "high-quality and reliable software products". </p>

<p>TechnoPark Corp. is outsourcing software development company with 
headquarters in the U.S., Naples, Florida, and software development center in 
the Ukraine, Dnepropetrovsk. Development of software for online payment systems 
(including mobile payments) is one of the company's core focuses.</p>

<p>The Certificate of Compliance is available at <ahref 
name="http://www.technoparkcorp.com/content/view/71/40/lang,en/">
http://www.technoparkcorp.com/content/view/71/40/lang,en/</ahref>.</p>

</text>
</article>