<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>intellectualproperty</term>

<title>Non-disclosure of information</title>
<label>Non-disclosure</label>
<intro>Read how our Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) protects your private information</intro>
<next>process/ipr/law</next>

<description>
</description>

<keywords>
</keywords>

<text>

	<p>During the project execution our project manager, project team, executive management and
	partners may need to have an access to the project information or information provided
	by you for the project purposes.</p>

	<p>Such information is confidential; that is stated in our software development
	contract which is signed between us.</p>

	<p>Our software development contract and Confidential Information means all proprietary information disclosed 
	or made available by one part to the other in the course of performing hereunder, 
	whether in written, email, instant message, orally by phone or personally, magnetic, photographic, 
	optical or other form, and whether now existing or hereafter created, including, without 
	limitation, all trade secrets, names and contacts of employees and partners, 
	technology, data, computer programs, processes, methods, operational procedures, plans, 
	strategies or results, and other information of a similar nature that is not generally disclosed by 
	such Party to the public.</p>
	
	<p>Confidential Information shall not include any information which:</p>
	
	<ul>
	<li>is proven by written evidence to have been in a receiving party's possession prior to disclosure by the other 
	Party;</li>
	<li>is received from a third party having the right to disclose such information; </li>
	<li>is or hereafter becomes public knowledge through no act or fault of a receiving party; or </li>
	<li>is proven by written evidence to have been independently developed by a receiving party without access to 
	the Confidential Information of the other party.</li>
	</ul>

	<p>Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) is signed between our company and you in order 
	to protect both parties against losses of such confidential information.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
	<c1 name="process/ipr/nda">NDA protects us both against information disclosure</c1>
	<c2 name="process/ipr/law">US Copyright Law guarantees your intellectual property rights</c2>
	<c3 name="process/ipr/security">Physical and documentary means exist to protect data on servers and in offices</c3>
</concepts>

</article>


