<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<date>2/12/09</date>

<invisible/>
<label>Four Symptoms</label>
<title>Four most severe symptoms of lost quality control</title>     

<keywords>
    cyclomatic complexity,
    code coverage,
    software quality,
    quality control,
    software metrics,
    continuous integration
</keywords>

<description>
    Quality-of-code in remote programming projects can be monitored 
    and controlled by means of instant metrics and motivation mechanisms. 
    TechnoPark Corp. has developed such a method.
</description>

<text>

    <p>Almost every software outsourcing programming contract experiences 
    the same problems with quality of software code produced 
    by remote programmers. Customers don't have enough programming skills 
    and spare time to check the quality-of-code regularly. Programmers 
    don't think too much about quality since the customer is far away.</p>

    <p>As a result, quality-of-code is out of the customer's control. There are 
    four severe symptoms of such a situation:</p>

    <ol>
        <li>You are afraid to change key programmers since each of them possesses some unique knowledge about your product;</li>
        <li>You can only hope that your code is of good quality because your coders say it is;</li>
        <li>You can't add new features freely since the product becomes unstable after every new change;</li>
        <li>You feel that if you want to get higher quality-of-code you have to change programmers.</li>
    </ol>
        
    <p>TechnoPark Corp. has developed a solution that returns control 
    over quality-of-code to the customer's hands. Special software built 
    into a continuous integration cycle collects the two most-valuable source 
    code metrics (Code Coverage and Cyclomatic Complexity) and converts their 
    values into bonuses for programmers. By doing this regularly and 
    automatically, the customer and the project team get a unique 
    level of control over quality-of-code.</p>
    
    <p>More details about the method are available on the TechnoPark Corp 
    website at <a href="http://www.technoparkcorp.com/innovations/metrics">http://www.technoparkcorp.com/innovations/metrics</a>. The method 
    can be implemented in new projects managed by TechnoPark Corp and 
    in currently running projects where TechnoPark Corp might play a role 
    as the project management contractor.</p>
    
    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a custom software development company that makes 
    complex full-scale project management simple and clear by means of automated innovative metrics.</p>

</text>
</article>