<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>rom</term>

<title>Rough order of magnitude estimate</title>
<label>ROM Estimate</label>
<intro>Learn more about ROM Estimate, our estimation and quotation methods</intro>
<next>stories</next>

<description>
    Rough order of magnitude estimate (ROM) gives preliminary information
    about project cost
</description>

<keywords>
    ROM estimate,
    rough order of magnitude,
    rough order magnitude,
    preliminary estimate of project size,
    what is ROM,
    cost estimation,
    project size estimation,
    project budget
</keywords>

<text>

    <p>When a project is started and Requirements are not specified in great detail,
    the exact project [Budget]({% href process/cost/budget %})
    can not be calculated without mistakes (due to the well-known [Cone of Uncertainty](http://www.construx.com/Page.aspx?hid=1648)).
    Concrete numbers in this stage will lead to an ineffective
    situation in which you or us may experience loss.</p>

    <p>To avoid the possibility of such an ineffective situation,
    we provide a Rough Order-of-Magnitude (ROM) Estimate of costs
    and time when Requirements are not specified in the early stages of the project.
    The ROM Estimate is based on
    [Vision]({% href process/scope/vision %}) document that includes
    a list of [Features]({% href process/scope/feature %}).</p>

    <p>The ROM Estimate includes the following project parameters
    which are the foundation for estimation:</p>

    <table>
        <tr>
            <th style="width: 100px;">Parameter</th>
            <th>Explanation</th>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Interval, staff-hours</td>
        <td>Project may be completed within this range if all Requirements
        will be within the scope specified by Vision document.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Accuracy, %</td>
        <td>ROM Estimate is created by three estimators. Accuracy equals to 100% minus the
        biggest difference between one individual estimate and the mean.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Time estimate, weeks</td>
        <td>Minimum and maximum duration of the project in weeks.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Retainer</td>
        <td>Amount of staff-hours required to complete Inception Phase in order to produce
        detailed Specification and exact project Budget.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>KSLOC estimated</td>
        <td>An estimate of Kilo Software Lines Of Code to be written in the project. We calculate
        and estimate only hand-written, non-empty, non-comment lines of code.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Unadjusted FPs</td>
        <td>Function Points as an output parameter from COCOMO-II estimate method. In a simplified approach,
        function points could be compared with software functions or class methods.</td>
        </tr>

        <tr>
        <td>Features, BC/WC/ML</td>
        <td>List of Features from Vision document that were used by estimators. Best Case (BC),
        Worst Case (WC), and Most Likely (ML) are the output numbers of three-point estimate method.
        The numbers are just programming staff-hours by the estimate of programmers.</td>
        </tr>

    </table>

    <p>In order to calculate the numbers above, we use our own patent-pending estimation method,
    that is based on
    [COCOMO-II Software Cost Estimation Technology](http://sunset.usc.edu/research/COCOMOII/),
    [PERT (Program Evaluation and Review Technique)](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Program_Evaluation_and_Review_Technique) and
    [Wideband Delphi](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wideband_delphi).</p>

    <p>Completion of the ROM Estimate takes up to 48 hours.</p>

    <p>Projects smaller than 1500 staff-hours and larger than 5,000 staff-hours are not subject to
    ROM Estimation. When Specification is defined and project scope is baselined,
    we use our innovative method for project cost estimating called
    "[Scope Champions]({% href innovations/scope-champions %})".</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c3 name="process/cost/rom">ROM Estimate is based on your preliminary Specifications provided</c3>
    <c4 name="process/cost/budget">Budget is a final estimation of project size and price</c4>
    <c5 name="process/scope/vision">Vision with a collection of Features is the only source for the ROM Estimate</c5>
</concepts>

</article>


