<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>08/19/06</date>

<title>CISP/SDP Cerfitication in September</title>

<description>Payment applications market gets new security standards compliant 
product. Recently released TechnoPark Corp.'s mobile payment software will 
pass Visa/MasterCard CISP/SDP Certification in September 2006.</description>

<text class="html">

<ul><small>
August 20, 2006 <ahref 
name="http://prweb.com/releases/pci_dss/TechnoPark/prweb426859.htm">
PRWeb.com Press Release Newswire</ahref> - New PCI DSS Compliant Payment 
Software Approaches the Market<br />
August 20, 2006 <ahref 
name="http://news.yahoo.com/s/prweb/20060820/bs_prweb/prweb426859">Yahoo.com 
News</ahref> - New PCI DSS Compliant Payment Software Approaches the 
Market<br />
August 22, 2006 <ahref 
name="http://www.indiaprwire.com/news/high-tech-security/20060822515-payment-
software.htm">IndiaPRWire.com</ahref> - A copy of our press release<br />
August 24, 2006 <ahref name="http://allpaynews.com/node/1471">AllPayNews.com
</ahref> - Payment applications market gets new security standards compliant 
product
</small></ul>

<p>It may seem that too much is said about online payment security; still the 
problem is a crucial one and is being globally ventilated. How to be sure my 
payment is secure? The question is burning for all the links of the chain: 
payment service providers, applications developers, merchants, and cardholders. 
</p>

<p>Today, there is a unified approach to security standards. Payment Card 
Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) is a list of unified standards and 
requirements for the industry. However, only 20% of the major industry-related 
companies are PCI DSS compliant. This is stimulated by mid-tier merchants' and 
service providers' ignorance of the certificate though they are the most 
vulnerable objects of attacks. According to WordPress' report, many payment 
industry players feel the standard is not clear or is not being applied 
prudently to encourage complete adoption.</p>

<p>Anyhow, PCI DSS must be the most comprehensive solution - and positively 
the best at this stage.  Visa together with world's major payment systems 
strongly encourages payment service providers, merchants and payment 
applications developers to pass the PCI DSS compliance certification in order 
to be able to guarantee high-level security to both their customers and 
partners.</p>

<p>Understanding the importance of security matter, TechnoPark Corp., an 
outsourcing software development company, has released mobile payment 
processing system which meets all the standards provided by PCI DSS. The 
system enables users to pay for goods and services using only their mobile 
phones, and provides a number of additional functions like statistics, 
notifications, etc. Laboratory testing assured the product's compliance, so 
it is about to be sent to Visa for certification.</p>

<p>PCI Data security standard was developed by Visa and MasterCard and accepted 
by other major players. It provides 12 basic standards aiming to stamp out 
debit and credit card fraud, by introducing strict security standards for 
handling and keeping cardholder data. The six general principles of PCI DSS 
include the following: build and maintain a secure network, protect cardholder 
data, maintain a vulnerability management program, implement strong access 
control measures, regularly monitor and test networks, maintain an information 
security policy. </p>

<p>In the article devoted to data security standards Joan Herbig, President and 
CEO of Cambia Security, a security policy enforcement provider, writes for CSO 
Magazine: "Embracing the PCI standard may sound like a big task, and you may 
wonder if it's even necessary for your business. However, before you fill up 
your dance card with other priorities, consider this: As of now, there is no 
known case of a PCI-compliant network being compromised."</p>

<p>For software developers Visa/MasterCard provides the PCI DSS Compliance 
Payment Application Certificate. Only 50 payment applications have been 
validated by today. On the intense and constantly growing market it sounds 
shocking. 50 is a tiny piece of all available products. </p>

<p>Moreover, the up-to-date list includes only 1 payment application for 
cellular phones - the most fast-growing industry's tenderfoot (A survey from 
Visa USA, reported in Bank Systems &amp; Technology, shows that 61% of the 
respondents ages 25 to 34 were interested in making purchases via their 
cellphones). Still the adoption of PCI Data security standard may dramatically 
intensify anti-fraud efforts. </p>

<p>Thus, the major payment systems recommend choosing PCI DSS compliant 
services and products. It must be a cue for US and European companies as well 
as worldwide outsourcing software development firms striving to offer 
high-quality products. In light of this, the introduction of TechnoPark Corp.'s 
MPPS software and its compliance validation, scheduled for September 2006, is a 
piece of important shift towards the consolidation of high standards of payment 
card industry. </p>

</text>
</article>