<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>10/25/06</date>

<title>Problems of Regional IT Companies to Be Studied at UOF</title>

<description>Ukrainian Outsourcing Forum (UOF) 2006 will take place in Kiev  
October 26-27. This year, problems and prospects of regional outsourcing IT 
companies will be highlighted among the other issues. TechnoPark Corp. 
(Dniepropetrovsk, Ukraine) will report on regional outsourcing problems. </description>

<text>

<p>UOF is the most important event for the offshore IT 
outsourcing sector of Ukraine, and is one of the most popular forums in the 
former USSR countries. 2006 marks the third time the Forum has been held, and it gathers 
progressively more participants from Ukraine, CIS, and Europe.  Once again, 
previous attendance records are going to be broken. The forum will 
be attended by companies from Ukraine, Russia, Belarus, Canada, USA, Denmark, 
Germany, Switzerland, Sweden, Italy, United Kingdom, Netherlands, India, 
Mexico, Saudi Arabia, Israel, South Africa, Egypt and Pakistan.</p>  

<p>The Ukraine is a new player in the global offshore outsourcing market, therefore 
the problems to discuss are numerous. The intensive two day program 
will include presentations and round-table discussions devoted to IT business 
development in the CIS, global IT market trends, marketing of outsourcing 
services, outsourcing of independent testing services to the Ukraine, human 
resource management, and other problems. </p> 

<p>This year one of the sections will be devoted to regional software 
development centers and their trends. In progress of the section's operation 
several presentations and round-table discussions, where every participant will 
have a chance to ask questions and share ideas concerning the highlighted 
issues, will be held. </p>

<p>TechnoPark Corp. will lay upon the tables the most burning problems of 
regional offshore outsourcing. In spite of the presentation's focus on the
Dnepropetrovsk Region, many discussed problems are similar in most companies 
all over Ukraine. "There are a lot of problems: qualification of personnel, 
low quality of software, small projects - all these are only a few of the thorniest 
issues," says Anna Stetsenko, HR Director at TechnoPark Corp.  </p> 

<p>During the presentation titled "Outsourcing Software Development in 
Dnepropetrovsk Region: Customer-driven Model"  TechnoPark Corp. will cover the 
most important problems of regional companies and provide its solutions. 
According to TechnoPark Corp., customer-driven process is the best means for 
stable growth and improvment of service quality. Today, western clients are no 
longer wary of outsourcing their projects to eastern Europe. But now they want 
to get proper communications and high-quality software.  </p>     

<p>There are basic aspects required from Ukrainian IT companies by 
customers from the US, western Europe, and other countries: standardization, 
certification, well arranged management and development processes, and quality 
assurance. From TechnoPark Corp., these are the factors which are worth being 
the core focus of developing regional software companies which are not able to 
compete with big development companies in the number of employees and scopes of 
marketing campaigns. Thus ISO standardization, partnership opportunities 
(Oracle, Microsoft), management and development technologies (XP, MSF, RUP, 
Agile) as well as certification of engineers and software products will be the 
key issues of the presentation. </p> 

<p>Besides these issues, market volume, opportunities and advantages of the 
market, integration with other regions, situation in other big regions 
(Kharkov, Lvov, Kiev, Donetsk, Odessa, Vinnitsa), labor market and staff 
training, current market environment and leading Ukrainian companies will be 
referred to.  </p>

<p>Summarizing the long-term work over the presentation, including market 
research, study of the majority of big and medium-size companies in the region, 
co-operation with universities, and examination of the industry's development 
dynamics, TechnoPark Corp.'s research team points the positive trends. "Despite 
the variety of problems, which are to be solved by IT Outsourcing industry in 
Dnepropetrovsk Region, without a doubt we are gradually transforming from 
'backyard production' to world-recognized standards, and improve quality of our 
products", assures Anna Stetsenko.</p>    

<p>The section devoted to regional software development centers will be open 
within the Ukrainian Outsourcing Forum on October 26. Odessa, Kharkov, Kiev, 
Lvov and Donetsk Regions will be presented there along with Dnepropetrovsk 
Region. </p>

</text>
</article>