<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<title>Schedule performance and variance indicator</title>
<label>SPI</label>
<intro>Learn how to track a project with Earned Value Analysis data</intro>
<next>process/time/iteration</next>

<description>
    Earned Value data helps us track project performance. SPI (EV/PV) is
    an indicator of project performance.
</description>

<keywords>
    SPI,
    earned value analysis,
    earned value,
    planned value,
    project performance tracking,
    continuous integration,
    software outsourcing,
    offshore development,
    distributed programming,
</keywords>

<text>

    <p>[Earned Value Analysis](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Earned_value_management)
    is a method of tracking the status of a project.
    It is based on numeric
    parameters and provides a transparent and un-biased snapshot of the project situation.
    [ The Schedule](/process/time/schedule)
    is tracked by means of Earned Value (EV) and Planned Value (PV) parameters.</p>

    <p>EV is calculated as the total amount of required planned staff-hours for those requirements that you
    already accepted.</p>

    <p>PV is calculated as a piece of the project [Budget](/process/cost/budget).
    The amount is shown in staff-hours that were planned
    to be spent by today (staff-hours are divided evenly across the completed requirements.)</p>

    <p>Consider the following example, we have 5 requirements, today is the 25th day of the project.
    The total Budget is 615 staff-hours,
    and total project duration is 40 days (this is a snapshot of requirements attributes table):</p>

    <table>
        <tr>
            <th>#</th>
            <th>Requirement</th>
            <th>Size</th>
            <th>Status</th>
        </tr>
        <tr><td>R1</td><td>User can manage account</td><td>145</td><td>accepted</td></tr>
        <tr><td>R2</td><td>User can upload video</td><td>80</td><td>accepted</td></tr>
        <tr><td>R3</td><td>Admin can manage users</td><td>120</td><td>accepted</td></tr>
        <tr><td>R4</td><td>Admin can view reports</td><td>180</td><td>implemented</td></tr>
        <tr><td>R5</td><td>Admin can filter users</td><td>90</td><td>specified</td></tr>
    </table>

    <p>EV is the sum of 145, 80 and 120 staff-hours (all of the requirements that are accepted so far).
    EV is equal to 345 staff-hours.</p>

    <p>PV is the result of 25/40 days that have been put into the project (0.625),
    and then multiplied by 615 staff-hours.
    PV equals to approximately 384 staff-hours.
    According to the plan,
    we have to deliver 384 accepted staff-hours to the customer on the 25th day of the project.</p>

    <p>SPI is calculated as EV/PV and equals to 345/384 = 0.898.
    That means that the project is behind
    schedule now and corrective actions are required.</p>

    <p>This example shows how the project can be tracked
    without excess technical details.
    This information (EV, PV and SPI) is presented to you
    at each Iteration Acceptance Meeting (by the end of each [Iteration](/process/time/iteration))
    and is available instantly online in our management software.</p>

    <p>The SPI should always be equal to or greater than 1.0.
    This is a key aspect for the project manager.
    If an SPI is less than 1.0, the project manager immediately impelements corrective action, which could be one of the
    following (depending on other project characteristics):</p>

    <ul>
        <li>Add more resources</li>
        <li>Change the scope by moving requirements to the next release</li>
        <li>Re-estimate the project and approve a new Schedule and Budget (worst variant)</li>
    </ul>

    <p>The numbers presented by an Earned Value analysis help you, the project team, and project manager
    to stay on the same page during the course of the whole project.</p>

    <p>Earned Value data is not meaningful during the [Inception Phase](/process/time/inception), when
    [Specification](/process/scope/specification) is not yet approved. Following the
    [LCO Milestone](/process/time/lco) is consensus, the project manager will start to calculate the SPI.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c1 name="process/time/schedule">Schedules are tracked with SPIs</c1>
    <c2 name="process/time/iteration">Earned Value numbers are provided by the end of each Iteation</c2>
    <c3 name="process/scope/matrix">Traceability Matrix is a basis for SPI calculation</c3>
</concepts>

</article>


