<?xml version="1.0"?>

<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    9/12/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->

<article>

<date>09/03/2007</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. to Attend CGO Conference</title>

<description>On September 6th and 7th of 2007, TechnoPark Corp.'s management will attend 
the Sixth Annual International Smart-Sourcing Conference organized by the CGO.</description>

<text>

    <p>By attending the Smart-Sourcing Conference, TechnoPark's management intends 
    to gain additional knowledge and experience in providing outsourcing services. TechnoPark will 
    also use this CGO event as an opportunity to introduce itself to IT outsourcing customers.</p>

    <p>The Sixth Annual International Smart-Sourcing Conference will take place in Atlantic 
    City, NJ. Its initiator, the Center for Global Outsourcing (CGO), is an international institution aimed 
    at promoting offshore outsourcing, and enhancing communication between outsourcing customers 
    and offshore vendors.</p>

    <p>In a statement on <ahref name="http://www.outsourceglobal.org/conference.htm">the Smart-Sourcing Conference's website</ahref>, 
    the organizers explain 
    their mission. "We are in the midst of a global outsourcing revolution. Global outsourcing has 
    become an accepted business strategy of both Multi National Corporations (MNCs) and Small 
    and Medium Sized Enterprises (SMEs). But as the world changes rapidly, global outsourcing 
    itself has begun to evolve, and it therefore becomes important to re-evaluate and 
    redefine it. This year, we discuss Smart-Sourcing; so that we can challenge 
    ourselves to think differently and be ahead of the curve in this exciting time 
    in the global marketplace."</p>

    <p>The conference will provide TechnoPark Corp. with opportunities for communication and the establishment 
    of partnerships with outsourcing clients, experts, and offshore outsourcing service providers. The 
    conference's keynote speakers include professionals in marketing, technology, and IT 
    management fields. The conference will discuss problems and case studies of offshore 
    IT outsourcing and healthcare outsourcing.</p>

</text>

</article>


