<?xml version="1.0" ?>

<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/11/07 Yegor: first version, created by Melody Platz

-->
<article>

<date>10/11/07</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. Collaborates with ExtraGet.biz on a PPC Optimizer</title>     

<description>TechnoPark Corp. creates individualized software tools for an online marketing website.</description>

<text>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. has improved online 
    marketing technology.  By building specialized software tools for ExtraGet.biz, 
    TechnoPark Corp. meets the needs of a growing Internet business community.</p>

    <p>ExtraGet.biz has launched a website devoted to advertising and marketing for 
    today's businessperson. ExtraGet.biz provides targeted business traffic, marketing 
    information, and a devoted management team to oversee services for its members.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. created the Pay-Per-Click Optimizer which is at the heart of 
    www.ExtraGet.biz.   This PPC optimizer, created especially for ExtraGet.biz, tracks 
    web traffic and improves the filtering of fake visits and clicks.  </p>

    <p>The Pay-Per-Click process allows marketers to target their advertising by 
    creating keywords.  If an Internet user searches for that keyword, the marketer's 
    advertisement will show up.  This helps the Internet user find what they need 
    and helps the marketer reach specific customers.</p>

    <p>TechnoPark had to understand the current PPC technology in order to 
    enhance it.  Project manager for TechnoPark Corp, Andrey Sadovsky, says "We did significant 
    research on web traffic and search engine traffic.  As a result we created a unique 
    module for fraudulent clicks filtering."   This new streamlined system allows both 
    the site user and the ExtraGet.biz member to find more value in their ExtraGet.biz experience.</p>

    <p>Online user experience is important because the competition between online marketing 
    directories can be tense. While the Internet has brought a stream of new customers to 
    many businesses, it has also allowed anyone with a website to set up an online marketing 
    tool.  By doing a quick search of the Internet, a user will find directories charging 
    outrageous fees, websites sporting misspellings and disjointed language, and services 
    that allow scammers to exploit their products.</p>

    <p>With the help of TechnoPark Corp.'s technology, ExtraGet.biz can offer specific business 
    traffic, professional service, and freedom from fraudulent clicks.</p>

    <p>ExtraGet Corp. is a premier Global internet marketer and reseller company based 
    in the Republic Of Panama.  TechnoPark Corp. is a US-based outsourcing software development 
    company with a development center in the Ukraine.</p>

</text>
</article>