<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>03/21/07</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. Becomes Member of RUSSOFT</title>

<description>TechnoPark Corp. has become an associate member of RUSSOFT
 Association. RUSSOFT is an international association of development
  companies aimed at promoting Russian, Ukrainian and Belarusian software
   services.</description>

<text>

<p>It is the major software association in the region uniting leading
 outsourcing software development companies. The Association's website
  <ahref name="http://www.russoft.org">RUSSOFT.org</ahref> provides software
   market studies and information about software development companies from
    the Ukraine, Belarus and Russia.</p>

<p>As a respected organization, RUSSOFT Association provides strict criteria
 for its members. Only companies that meet the criteria are granted
  membership. By becoming a RUSSOFT Association member, TechnoPark Corp. proved
   its high level of services and products.</p>

<p>The Association unites about 80 companies now, including TechnoPark Corp.
 From RUSSOFT Association: "We maintain the highest level of international
  standards, professional training and quality control, whereas our companies
   are the absolute leaders by CMMI/ISO certification in Europe. Their
    capabilities have been proven by long term customer relationships and
     partnerships with such companies as IBM, Boeing, SAP, Italtel, CSC and
      others." </p>

<p>The outsourcing industry is swiftly developing in eastern Europe. This
 development is stimulated by high intellectual potential derived from the powerful
  military sector of the USSR, low cost of IT personnel, governmental support,
   and cultural ties with western Europe. </p>

<p>Today, small and medium-sized businesses are major customers of eastern
 European offshoring companies. Major corporations still hesitate about
  offshoring software projects to the region, because of the lack of knowledge
   about the area. To solve this problem, IT outsourcing associations are established,
    and international forums and conferences are held in the leading
     outsourcing locations of eastern Europe which are Russia, Belarus and
      Ukraine.</p>

<p>RUSSOFT is the largest association in the region, and membership is only granted
 to reliable and mature IT outsourcing companies. For an outsourcer searching
  for a partner in the region, RUSSOFT membership should guarantee high quality
   products and processes as well as reliability of the provider. Benefits of
    membership for outsourcing software development service providers include
     additional promotional opportunity and communication of experience with
      other industry players.</p>

<p>Besides RUSSOFT, TechnoPark Corp. is a member of Ukrainian High-Tech
 Initiative - the biggest association of IT outsourcing companies in the Ukraine.
  TechnoPark Corp. is a standing speaker at the annual Ukrainian Outsourcing
   Forum (UOF) held by the Ukrainian High-Tech Initiative. From TechnoPark
    Corp., membership in associations and participation in forums and
     conferences are necessary not only for the company's self-promotion, but
      also for the promotion of IT Outsourcing Industry in the Ukraine, as long
       as the country has a very high potential to become one of the world's
    outsourcing leaders in the next few years.</p>

</text>
</article>