<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>01/18/07</date>

<title>Outsourcing to Ukraine: 2006 results and 2007 expectations</title>

<description>2006 showed that IT outsourcing remained one of the most dynamic
 fields in the Ukrainian economy. Because of the growing requirements for the
  service, 2007 is also expected to be successful for the industry. </description>

<text>
<p>The Information Technology market in the Ukraine has been growing stably during
 the last five years. Although internal customers still cannot afford to order large IT projects, 
 Ukrainian IT products are progressively more desired in
 western countries. The United States and western Europe are unalterably the
 well-established importers of software development services from the
 Ukraine.  </p>

<p>The growth of IT industry export totaled 60% and rose to $280 million in
 2006; the growth of IT market totaled 25-30%. According to the IDC forecast,
 Ukrainian Information Technology market is expected to grow 15-17% and reach
 $2.4-2.5 million in 2007. This means that the outsourcing service market is going
 to maintain stable growth. </p>

<p>The successful development of Information Technology Outsourcing Industry
 in the Ukraine results from a number of advantageous factors in the country. </p>

<p>Despite the increase in developer's salaries and general price inflation
 in 2006, software development costs are still highly competitive and
 attractive for western customers. The attractive prices are accompanied
 with progressively improving quality of products and knowledge of
 developers. </p>

<p>Still, offering low costs is the priority only for small and medium-sized western
 companies when they choose outsourcing service provider. These are the kind of
 customers who will be critical for maintaining Ukrainian IT services export volume
 in 2007. In order to attract big investors, governmental programs
 stimulating country's IT industry development and making up positive image
 of the Ukrainian developers in the world need to be conducted. The
 majority of U.S. and western European big business owners still consider
 risks of IT outsourcing to the Ukraine to be very high. Several years
 are needed to attract them to the country. </p>

<p>Nevertheless, small and medium-sized customers are good prospectives.
 IDC forecasts the increase of small and medium-sized businesses' (SMB) role
 for providers searching for new markets. </p>

<p>Another factor which is expected to contribute to the development of the
 Ukrainian Information Technology market is the unstable political situation in
 the Middle East. The permanent threat of war conflicts in the region leads
 to the surrender of cooperation with the traditional outsourcing
 market leaders: India, Israel, Pakistani and other Middle Eastern
 countries. The reallocation of orders will start in the near
 future, providing Ukraine with a good chance to present itself as a
 reliable and prospective service provider at the global market level.
 Because of the political instability in the Middle East, interest from
 eastern and central European countries has increased.  </p>

<p>The similarity of cultural code, traditions, and religion are an important
 advantage for outsourcers to work with the country. U.S. and western European
 customers like the western mentality Ukrainians offer and small time-zone
 differences. Thus, a new trend called "nearshoring" is a prospective
 direction for the Ukraine. Nearshoring is an offshore outsourcing to
 countries situated near the customer's country. It is popular in 
 developed western European countries like Germany.
 The former USSR republics which include Ukraine are within eyeshot of
 customers who may start exploiting nearshoring</p>

<p>Numerous Information Technology conferences and forums evidence the
 increased interest to the Ukraine around the globe. Ukrainian Outsourcing
 Forum, which is one of the most important outsourcing events, has expanded
 its borders and hosted participants from the U.S., Europe and Asia in 2006.
The  Ukrainian showcase at the international outsourcing exhibition CeBIT 2006
 was another important shift. </p>

<p>Due to all of these factors, the Ukraine was included into the five most attractive
 outsourcing directions for some western countries in 2006. </p>

<p>The progress of the IT outsourcing decentralization process is an obvious trend.
 Regions develop dynamically and compete with the capital, Kiev. It helps to
 keep prices down along with improving the services quality. Regional
 companies are traditionally small with the staff of no more than 100
 employees, however, these are the companies making up the basis of the
 Information Technology Industry in the Ukraine, where big players can
 be counted on the fingers of one hand presently. </p>

<p>That is why swiftly developing medium-sized companies determine the
 development of IT outsourcing industry in the Ukraine now. From TechnoPark
 Corp. Management, the company's profit has grown by 70% in 2006. TechnoPark
 Corp. is outsourcing software development company. Software development
 center is located in Dnepropetrovsk, Ukraine, and company's headquarters
 is based in the U.S., Florida. Due to the U.S. based office, it is easy for
 the company to find and contact western clients. A number of successful
 projects implemented by TechnoPark Corp. evidence that there are mature
 companies able to provide reliable and stable cooperation in the
 field of offshore software development outsourcing in the Ukraine.    
     </p>

<p>Due to growing interest in the Ukraine, the number of articles devoted
 to the country as an attractive IT outsourcing direction increase in the U.S.
 and European mass media. "The country is quickly becoming a home for
 offshore development, with outsourcing turnover apparently growing at 200
 to 300 per cent annually. Locations that buck the downward trend will
 provide competitive sourcing solutions for IT directors. Ukraine might
 well be one of such centres," writes British online magazine
 <ahref name="http://www.itweek.co.uk">ITWeek.co.uk</ahref>. </p>

<p>A publication devoted to outsourcing to Eastern Europe published at
 <ahref name="http://www.global-outsourcing.blogspot.com">
 Global-outsourcing.blogspot.com</ahref> reads that "The attractive offshore
 work centers in eastern
 Europe include Russia, Ukraine, Poland, Belarus
 and the Baltic. These markets not only offer low cost skilled labor forces,
 but also an attractive regulatory environment with a close proximity and
 cultural ties to western Europe." </p>

<p>The Ukrainian Information Technology Outsourcing Industry will continue growing.
 Even though experts foresee the general decrease of IT outsourcing needs in
 the global market, the Ukraine has good chances of fidning its niche and
 developing outsourcing services due to political stability and great
 intellectual resources.</p>
</text>
</article>