<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/03/07 Amy M. Wolfe-text edit

-->
<article>

<date>05/24/07</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp. Prepares for ISO Certification</title>

<description>May 24, 2007 -- TechnoPark Corp. (TPC) recently began
 preparing to obtain ISO 9001 certification, a process expected to take
 approximately 7 months.</description>

<text>

<p>To obtain certification, TPC must demonstrate that its policies are in compliance
 with ISO standards and provide proof of a successful internal and third-party
 audit.  ISO 9001 is one of the standards of the ISO 9000 family, introduced
 by <ahref name="http://www.iso.org">ISO (International Organization for
 Standardization)</ahref>.</p>

<p>In the next month, TPC will finish outlining changes and improvements that
 are required within the company to meet certification. </p>

<p>The company currently is reviewing qualifications of five auditors and will
 make a selection in the coming weeks. The third-party audit and application
 for certification are slated for January 2008. The certification process will
 review TPC's business processes, recording, quality control, assurance,
 defects detection, and more. </p>

<p>"We realize the great importance of ISO certification. It will bring our
 clients incontestable quality guarantee and confirm reliability of their
 partnership with TechnoPark Corp.," says Maria Vinogradova, Quality Assurance
 Manager in TechnoPark Corp. "There is no doubt that we will pass the audit
 successfully." Vinogradova continues, "Presently the company has strong
 internal standards recorded in number of TPC Policy documents, so only
 small improvements are needed to become compliant with ISO 9001 
 requirements".</p>

<p>ISO 9001 Certification is the next step in the company's goal of obtaining
 CMMI Certification in the future. </p>

<ul>
<small><ahref name="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/ISO_9001">ISO 9001 in
 Wikipedia</ahref>:
<br />ISO 9000 is a family of standards for quality management systems.
 ISO 9000 is maintained by ISO, the International Organization for
 Standardization and is administered by accreditation and certification
 bodies. For a manufacturer, some of the requirements in ISO 9001 (which
 is one of the standards in the ISO 9000 family) would include:
<li>a set of procedures that cover all key processes in the business;</li>
<li>monitoring manufacturing processes to ensure they are producing quality
 product;</li>
<li>keeping proper records;</li>
<li>checking outgoing product for defects, with appropriate corrective action
 where necessary;</li>
<li>regularly reviewing individual processes and the quality system itself
 for effectiveness; </li>
<li>facilitating continual improvement.</li>
</small>
</ul>

</text>
</article>