<?xml version="1.0" ?>

<!-- 
    Version tracking section:

    10/11/07 Yegor: first version, created by Melody Platz

-->
<article>

<date>12/20/07</date>

<title>TechnoPark Corp.  Hires Taleo for Talent Solutions</title>     

<description>TechnoPark Corp. installs Taleo management solutions on their website.</description>

<text>

    <p>Naples, FL, December 20, 2007 - TechnoPark Corp. now has an easy to use employee 
    recruitment system featured on their website at www.technoparkcorp.com.  TechnoPark Corp. has 
    hired Taleo to streamline their recruitment process.  </p>

    <p>Taleo, <ahref name="http://www.taleo.com">www.taleo.com</ahref>, allows companies to recruit new employees on their website by simply using 
    their web browser.  Companies using Taleo for improved human resource results include 
    Hewlett-Packard, Cornell University, and Hyatt Hotels and Resorts. </p>

    <p>By using Taleo, TechnoPark Corp. won't have to install software or spend time 
    learning complicated recruitment systems.  Within the first 48 hours of using Taleo, 
    most companies are able to start processing applications from perspective employees.</p>

    <p>For TechnoPark Corp, this means management will spend less time on paperwork and 
    more time on finding the best employees available.  As a software development company 
    that employs premiere people from around the globe, TechnoPark Corp. believed 
    that it was imperative to have the most efficient system for finding talent in place. </p>

    <p>"I'll be able to create virtual teams," said project manager for TechnoPark Corp, 
    Victor Petrovsky.  "I can manage personnel remotely without installing any special 
    software on my servers."</p>

    <p>TechnoPark Corp. is a US-based outsourcing software development company with a development 
    center in the Ukraine.  They recently received their ISO 9001- 2000 Certification. 
    TechnoPark Corp. uses the most popular object-oriented platforms and technologies: 
    Microsoft .Net, AJAX, Adobe Flash and Flex, PHP.  They have been in operation since 2001.</p>

</text>
</article>