<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>rom</term>

<title>Two-step quotation process</title>
<label>Cost Management</label>
<intro>Read how projects are quoted, estimated, and paid</intro>
<next>about/why</next>

<description>
    We estimate cost of a project in two steps, minimizing the
    risk of over and under estimation. ROM estimate preceeds Budget.
</description>

<keywords>
    cost estimate,
    project cost,
    project cost management plan,
    ROM Estimate,
    budget,
    quoation
</keywords>

<text>

    <p>We do projects in fixed-price contracts, meaning that the price is defined 
    according to <a href="${url:process/scope}">scope</a> definition
    and is not changed unless there are changes to <a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a>. 
    We take all risks of cost overrun so that you
    pay only the price defined in project <a href="${url:process/cost/budget}">Budget</a>.</p>

    <p>Our two-step quotation process has a number of important advantages:</p>

    <ul>
        <li>Final budget is optimal, without extra costs and reserves</li>
        <li>Guarantees "win-win" outcome for you and us</li>
        <li>Avoids cost overrun</li>
        <li>Guarantees project success</li>
    </ul>
    
    <p>We calculate and communicate all project costs in staff-hours. Actual monetary size of
    project is a multiple of staff-hours and <a href="${url:process/cost/prices}">price per hour</a>.</p>

    <p>Cost is estimated in two steps:</p>

    <ol>
        <li><a href="${url:process/cost/rom}">ROM Estimate</a> and Retainer</li>
        <li>Budget</li>
    </ol>

    <p>The ROM Estimate is provided to you in response to your informal request 
    and is based on the <a href="${url:process/scope/vision}">Vision</a> document.
    ROM Estimate gives a range (low and high boundary) of the expected Budget. 
    You approve the range
    and the project team performs <a href="${url:process/scope/requirement}">requirements</a> gathering 
    and analysis during the <a href="${url:process/scope/inception}">Inception Phase</a>.  
    These steps result in the creation of a
    <a href="${url:process/scope/srs}">SRS</a> document.</p>

    <p>When the SRS is ready and you approved it, the project team estimates project Budget
    as an exact amount of staff-hours. The Budget can only be within the range provided in ROM Estimate. 
    Upon your approval of the Budget, the project continues.</p>

    <p>If you don't approve the Budget for any reason, you pay only the Retainer, which
    covers the efforts for Requirements gathering and Specification development.</p>

    <p><a href="${url:process/cost/model}">Payments</a> are made according to Milestones defined in the
    <a href="${url:process/time/schedule}">Schedule</a>, which is approved together with the Budget.</p>

    <p>Budget covers all costs, including programming, requirements analysis, management,
    project management, architecture and design, testing and quality assurance.</p>
        
</text>

<concepts>
    <c3 name="process/cost/rom">ROM Estimate is based on preliminary specification you provided</c3>
    <c4 name="process/cost/budget">Budget is a final estimation of project size and price, no changes can be made later without your approval</c4>
    <c5 name="process/scope/specification">Specification is the foundation of final Budget estimation</c5>
    <c7 name="process/time/schedule">You approve Schedule together with Budget and Specification</c7>
</concepts>

</article>


          