<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugaenko <egor@technoparkcorp.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>quality</term>

<title>Quality is planned, assured and controlled</title>
<label>Quality Management</label>
<intro>Read about Quality Management and cost of quality we suggest</intro>
<next>process/cost</next>

<description>
</description>

<keywords>
</keywords>

<text>

	<p>Quality is the degree of conformance of <a href="${url:process/warranty/deliverables}">Deliverables</a> to 
	<a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a>. The goal of a project is
	to deliver software products with an acceptable level of Quality on time. Acceptable, according to our
	software development contract, means that Quality
	is 95% or greater.</p>

	<p>Defects in software decrease the level of Quality and shall be removed by the project team. We take preventive
	actions to minimize Defects. Revealed Defects are removed during project lifecycle.</p>

	<p>An estimated number of Defects are planned when a project is started and is based on the
	amount of Functional Requirements. Testers work with the software product until the estimated number 
	of Defects are found. This gives us confidence that software is delivered without
	critical hidden Defects.</p>

	<p>Any type of software has an unlimited number of Defects.  Some of these
	are critical and some are minor. In the iterative and 
	<a href="${url:process/communication/incremental}">incremental</a> delivery process we use to
	find the planned amount of Defects, we provide an optimal service 
	in the limited amount of <a href="${url:process/time}">time</a> given. Regardless, all critical Defects are 
	to be found and removed.</p>

	<p>Defects are tracked in a Defects Tracking System, which you have an access to. During 
	the whole project lifecycle you may view Defects and add their own records to this database.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
	<c1 name="process/warranty/deliverables">Deliverables are conformant to Specification and are high quality</c1>
	<c2 name="process/scope/specification">Specification is a message to the project team about quality and Deliverables</c2>
	<c3 name="process/communication/incremental">Incremental delivery is a method of quality improvement</c3>
</concepts>

</article>


