<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>schedule</term>

<title>How in-time delivery is assured</title>
<label>Time Management</label>
<intro>Review our time management methods</intro>
<next>process/cost</next>

<description>
    Iterative time management gives project team and our customer more
    flexibility in plans. In the same time it gives more stability for
    the whole project.
</description>

<keywords>
    time management,
    time management plan,
    time tracking,
    project plan,
    network diagram,
    schedule,
    iteration,
    iteration plan,
    software outsourcing,
    offshore development,
    distributed programming,
</keywords>

<text>

    <p>Talented and motivated engineers, programmers, designers and architects may
    fail to complete a project and miss important milestones if they don't have a project manager
    who manages time properly. Nowadays in the software industry this happens during the course of many projects.
    We pay great attention to planning, monitoring, and controlling of time in our projects.</p>

    <p>Right after a <a href="${url:process/cost/rom}">ROM Estimate</a> is approved and the project is started, 
    we plan the <a href="${url:process/time/inception}">Inception Phase</a>. 
    Usually, when the project is started, there is a lack of details about system requirements. 
    Accurate planning can be done only after the scope definition and risk analysis are completed, that's why we need to conduct the 
    Inception Phase before <a href="${url:process/time/schedule}">Schedule</a> development.</p>
    
    <p>The main goal of our Inception Phase is to create <a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a>, 
    identify <a href="${url:process/risks}">Risks</a>, 
    calculate <a href="${url:process/cost/budget}">Budget</a>, and build a
    Schedule. Sometimes, in order to define the Schedule, it's necessary to develop a baseline of key architectural software concepts
    during the Inception Phase.</p>

    <p><a href="${url:process/time/lco}">LCO Milestone</a> happens following the end of Inception Phase, when
    the Specification is ready and a Schedule is defined. The Schedule is a one-page table that lists the
    <a href="${url:process/time/iteration}">Iterations</a> and Milestones. 
    As soon as the customer signs the Schedule, it obtains the status of a contractual provision
    and can't be missed.</p>

    <p align="center"><tikz>
\begin{tikzpicture}
    [auto, thick]

    \newcommand{\thewidth}{2.2cm}
    \newcommand{\theheight}{1cm}

    \tikzstyle{iteration} = [block, 
        text width=\thewidth, 
        anchor=north west,
        minimum height=\theheight]

    \tikzstyle{vline} = [dashed, draw=tpcBlue]

    \foreach \x/\title in {0/{Inception Phase}, 1/{Interation 2}, 2/{Interation 3}, 3/{Interation 4}, 4/{Last Iteration}} {
        \node [iteration] (Iteration\x) at (\x*\thewidth,-\x*\theheight) {\title};
        \draw [vline] (\x*\thewidth,\theheight) -- (\x*\thewidth,-6*\theheight);
    }

    \draw [line, triangle 60-triangle 60] (0, -6*\theheight) -- node [above, fill=white, above=-0.3cm] {project lifecycle} (5*\thewidth, -6*\theheight);

    \node [fill=white, above left=of Iteration0.north] (note1) {Project start};
    \node [fill=white, above=2cm of Iteration2, text width=4cm] (note2) {Specification, Schedule, Budget, and Risks are approved};
    \node [fill=white, above=2cm of Iteration4, text width=4cm] (note3) {Iteration Acceptance Meeting with new Build and project tracking data};
    \node [fill=white, below=1.3cm of Iteration4, text width=4cm] (note4) {Acceptance Statement is signed, project is closed};

    \draw [-angle 90] (note1) -- (Iteration0.west);
    \draw [-angle 90] (note2) -- (Iteration0.east);
    \draw [-angle 90] (note3) -- (Iteration1.east);
    \draw [-angle 90] (note3) -- (Iteration2.east);
    \draw [-angle 90] (note3) -- (Iteration3.east);
    \draw [-angle 90] (note4) -- (Iteration4.south east);

\end{tikzpicture}
    </tikz></p>

    <p>The objective of each Iteration is to implement, test, and deliver a certain part of the product functionality.
    Iteration normally takes 8-12 working days and starts with a fine-grained Iteration Plan, which is
    shown to you and is used to track the progress during the project.</p>

    <p>The Iteration Plan is focused on the Iteration objective as defined in the Schedule, and uses the
    WBS and Network Diagram methods for planning.</p>

    <p>By the end of each Iteration, we conduct an Iteration Acceptance Meeting, where a
    <a href="${url:process/time/spi}">SPI</a> is presented to you in conjunction with the risk monitoring results. 
    The project is transparently 
    monitored and tracked with an SPI, which is based on the functional requirements and their status of completion.</p>

    <p>Any changes to the Milestones will produce a new version of the Schedule, which you shall
    sign to make it effective.</p>


</text>

<concepts>
    <c1 name="process/time/schedule">The Schedule is a coarse-grained plan of a project</c1>
    <c2 name="process/time/lco">Lifecycle Objectives (LCO) Milestone is when the Schedule is to be approved</c2>
    <c3 name="process/time/inception">Inception Phase specifies Requirements, identifies Risks and builds Schedule</c3>
    <c4 name="process/time/iteration">Iteration is the shortest time-slice in a project</c4>
    <c5 name="process/time/spi">Schedule Performance Index (SPI) indicates project status</c5>
</concepts>

</article>


