<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>milestone</term>

<title>Smallest unit of time in schedule</title>
<label>Iteration</label>
<intro>Read about Iteration Plans (WBS, Gantt Chart, Network Diagram, etc.)</intro>
<next>process/time/schedule</next>

<description>
    Iteration is a smallest unit of time planning, and constists of 
    activities. Iteration Plan includes objective of iteration, work
    packages from WBS, network diagram and gantt chart.
</description>

<keywords>
    iteration plan,
    iteration,
    WBS,
    work package,
    network diagram,
    gantt chart,
    bar chart, 
    iteration objective,
    continuous integration,
    software outsourcing,
    offshore development,
    distributed programming,
</keywords>

<text>

    <p><a href="${url:process/time/schedule}">Schedule</a> consists of Iterations. 
    Each Iteration is a simple and atomic piece of time spent on
    project activities by the project team.</p>

    <p>The goal of Iteration is to perform all of the project disciplines and 
    deliver the new product increment - software with new functionality. 
    Each Iteration conducts refinement on requirements, architecture analysis and design,
    programming, testing, and deployment. 
    Upon conclusion, the Iteration finishes with new workable software build.</p>

    <p>Normal Iteration duration is 10 working days. 
    Sometimes we do smaller and longer Iterations.
    Iteration starts with an Iteration Plan, which is a fine-grained plan, and includes:</p>
    
    <ul>
        <li>Objective of Iteration </li>
        <li>Work packages from Work Breakdown Structure (WBS)</li>
        <li>Roles and responsibilities</li>
        <li>Activity list with cost and duration estimations</li>
        <li>Network diagram</li> 
        <li>Bar chart (Gantt chart)</li>
    </ul>

    <p>An Iteration Plan is created by the project manager and team. 
    The Iteration Plan is then committed by the 
    project team - such commitment is a must for all Iterations.</p>

    <p>An Iteration Acceptance Meeting finishes the Iteration and is conducted online with your participation. 
    The key purpose of this meeting is to present you the project status and risk monitoring results.
    Earned Value technique is used to evaluate and indicate the project status. 
    <a href="${url:process/time/spi}">SPI</a> and <a href="${url:process/cost}">CPI</a> numbers
    will help all parties involved to understand the actual project status.</p>

    <p>During Iteration execution, the project manager sends you <a href="${url:process/communication/dailyreport}">daily reports</a> 
    with a list of activities completed during the day.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c2 name="process/time/schedule"> The Schedule is a coarse-grained plan of a project and a container of Iterations.</c2>
    <c5 name="process/time/spi">The Schedule Performance Index (SPI) derived from an Earned Value Analysis helps to track project</c5>
</concepts>

</article>


