<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2008, TechnoPark Corp., Florida, USA
 * All rights reserved. THIS IS PRIVATE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are PROHIBITED
 * without prior written permission from the author. This product may NOT be used anywhere
 * and on any computer except the server platform of TechnoPark Corp. located at
 * www.technoparkcorp.com. If you received this code occacionally and without intent to use
 * it, please report this incident to the author by email: privacy@technoparkcorp.com or
 * by mail: 568 Ninth Street South 202 Naples, Florida 34102, the United States of America,
 * tel. +1 (239) 243 0206, fax +1 (239) 236-0738.
 *
 * @author Yegor Bugayenko <egor@tpc2.com>
 * @copyright Copyright (c) TechnoPark Corp., 2001-2009
 * @version $Id$
 *
-->

<article>

<term>preliminaryspecification</term>

<title>Vision document is a preliminary Specification of scope</title>
<label>Vision</label>
<intro>Learn how high-level requirements are defined in Vision document</intro>
<next>process/scope/feature</next>

<description>
    Vision is a preliminary scope definition document, that we create
    before the contract is signed.
</description>

<keywords>
    vision,
    features,
    project charter,
    scope definition,
    preliminary scope definition,
    continuous integration,
    software outsourcing,
    offshore development,
    distributed programming,
</keywords>

<text>

    <p>Each customer has their own understanding of task definition.  Customers also use their own format
    for documentation. Sometimes, such documentation is properly formatted and presented, and
    sometimes it is not. We use a uniform and standard format for the preliminary scope
    definition. It is short, simple, and very clear - we call it the Vision.</p>

    <p>The Vision document is a two page file that includes a description of the project,
    list of <a href="${url:process/scope/feature}">Features</a>, key risks, assumptions, and architectural concepts. 
    It is possible to present any product scope in this simple format,
    even if the product is very large.</p>

    <p>The Vision document is not a fully-dressed <a href="${url:process/scope/specification}">Specification</a> and cannot be used by 
    developers for the purpose of programming. The Vision is used by the system analyst, project manager,
    customer, and other stakeholders for the following reasons:</p>

    <anchor name="list">
    <ul>
        <li>To define the boundaries of the product.</li>
        <li>To gain an understanding of project goals.</li>
        <li>To identify key stakeholders and their needs.</li>
    </ul>
    </anchor>

    <p>A system analyst usually spends up to five hours developing the Vision.</p>

</text>

<concepts>
    <c1 name="process/scope/feature">Feature is a top-level user requirement</c1>
    <c3 name="process/scope/specification">Specification details Vision</c3>
    <c5 name="process/cost/rom">ROM Estimate is based on Features</c5>
</concepts>

</article>



